Exquisite me.
Oh.
I have an idea.
Nice.
That is a definite way to gain access.
No!
What is happening?
Go through the thing!
Bomb it!
Maybe I am angering the gods or something.
I need to get close.
I don't have a... Oh my god!
Listen to that rumble.
That's nice.
Oh my god!
Huh?
What if I do it like this way?
No!
The good thing about the tentacles is it will show you when you take damage.
Yeah.
I'm scared.
I want
to get off Mr. Bones while I ride.
It's gonna explode, isn't it?
Yeah.
I'm so fucking dead.
Oh no!
He looked different.
Fill it up with this.
Oh, that was bad.
I'm gonna die.
Oh no.
The greed.
What the?
Is that a trap?
What's happening?
What just happened?
Oh yeah.
Dig for me.
Dig for... Yes!
Dig for... What's this?
Concentrated mana.
Dig for me.
Go, come on.
I was just doing that.
Oh no!
Oh!
I knew that would happen.
Fuck.
What do we have down here?
Yo, what's that?
Excuse me?
It's raining blood.
Hallelujah!
Oh my god, that's it.
Oh, it's over.
It's over.
Kill him.
Oh my god, it's over.
Oh no.
Oh my god.
Yo, what the hell?
Are you causing trouble?
Oh my god.
What a shot.
Bombs for you.
Shoot that guy.
Oh my god.
Oh well.
Boom!
Wow!
I'm about to die.
Yeah, it's over.
Okay.
I don't know what I am, but I like it.
Look at all that gold.
Oh, it's catching fire.
That's a little bit sketch.
Do it anyway.
No, I was greedy.
I thought I could survive.
I couldn't.
Look at all that sweet gold.
But, there's a bunch of acid.
Let's hover it right above it.
Oh, that was risky.
I'm on fire now.
I'm on fire.
Fill me.
Oh no, that's confusing.
Exquisite me.
That's for you, sir.
Wow, what a shot.
Holy shit.
I don't trust my machine gun that much.
Where are you?
Oh yeah, look at that stuff.
Looks cool though.
Oh, there's a candle left.
Huh, I'm a sheep.
Fly a little sheep.
Run.
Oh no, it's one of those guys.
What the fuck?
Is this water, isn't it?
Oh fuck, it's not.
I hit you.
Wait, he spawned a bunch.
Fuck, I killed myself.
Oh no.
Now I'm just going deeper and deeper here.
Shit.
There's no way we're going to survive this.
I don't know what this is.
Oh my lord.
Ah, fuck.
Ah, I'm stuck.
Oh yeah, man, that's ripped.
I expected that.
We've been there.
Oops, what did you come from?
Sir, I'm dying.
I'm almost dead.
I'm actually going to die.
Uh-oh.
Oh, fuck.
Fuck you.
Oh, no, it's over.
It's over.
I'm dying here.
Huh?
Oh, that's acid, it's not water.
Fuck.
That scares me a little bit.
I'm going to shut in with my first one because it's a lot of...
Oh, what?
Okay.
This is the saw blade challenge with one HP.
Holy shit.
What?
Back up, back up.
Oh, he's still shooting projectiles.
Holy.
I may have fucked up.
I think I'm dead.
The portal is there.
I have an out if I want it.
Holy shit.
Never mind.
Hey, yo, what if I have an idea?
Hey.
Okay, whatever.
Yeah, they are angry.
Oh, he came fast.
He came fast.
Oh, no, I went up here anyway.
I'm an idiot.
I'm totally going to die.
Fuck me.
I'm being saved by the projectile repulsion field.
I'm 4 HP.
I don't know what to do.
I'm drowning.
Well, that was bad.
It does.
I'm not taking damage from these.
And I take it back.
Dude, they heal.
Bam.
Whoops.
Oh,
what?
Exquisite me?
Oh, this thing is spawning them.
I don't like that at all.
I'm stuck.
Damn it.
I don't know what's happening.
There's something wrong with my character.
What the fuck is going on?
I'm scared of fire right now.
We're leaving.
Just go.
Holy shit.
He's after me.
Fuck you, man.
Fuck you, melee.
He punched me in the face.
If I touch the enemies, I die, right?
I'm just going to damage him.
It reflects off.
I'm dead.
It's over.
Run.
No, man.
Uh-oh.
There's a bunch of enemies down there.
Oh, no.
Holy shit.
We're done.
We're done here.
100%.
We're done.
There's no way.
Yeah.
There's a bunch of hammerses.
Wait, why is that slowing down so much?
Look at the projectiles.
Uh-oh.
There's a thingy.
What the hell is happening here?
Oh.
What
is it about this place?
Yeah.
Kill me.
Fucking kill me.
I hate this place.
I'm never coming to this place again.
I'm done.
Is that too risky?
God damn it.
This is the ultimate wand experimenter.
That's for you.
Oh, the rocks are getting absorbed.
No.
Heal me up.
Oh, god.
Oh, well, this only goes in diagonal shit.
Where'd you go?
Where have you gone?
Where did the wand go?
Oh, you fuck.
I will not go through that portal.
I am fighting this guy with one HP.
Wish me luck, guys.
This duel is happening.
He doesn't get... show me.
Uh, no.
I take my own life.
Whoa, that's a lot of freezing vapor.
Shit.
I have an idea.
Watch this.
Oh, oh my god.
Hold on.
We're gonna run a little bath here.
I'm not fucking done.
Plop.
And another plop here.
Then we're gonna plop up here.
And we're gonna plop here.
And one plop maybe right here.
All right, let's try.
Call me Silma.
Oh god.
Well, okay then.
Yeah, that's uh...
Oh, hi.
I didn't see you there.
I was just perusing my map and I realized that I'm missing something.
In fact, I'm missing a lot.
I'm missing this.
I didn't even fill out the ancient laboratory or the frozen expanse or whatever it was called.
There's actually a bunch of stuff.
I also know there's stuff somewhere else.
Basically, I have a lot of work to do is what I'm saying.
What's up, people?
What is going on?
Dwight Kurt Schrute.
What's up, man?
Hello, I'm watching your Subnautica playthrough right now.
I got notified of this.
Are you watching the original Subnautica or the below zero one?
In any case, thank you for watching that.
I hope you enjoy it.
Yeah, I didn't add the latest deaths yet, uh, Eugere.
I'll do it soon.
You didn't see the map yet, Qali?
I've been working on it for a while.
But you know what?
I started working on it quite late in... if you consider the amount of time I spent on Noiter in total.
So that's why I didn't add any of the very early stuff I found.
The original?
Nice.
The original is a masterpiece.
Such a fantastic game.
I hope you enjoy it.
Shadow Fantasy 58.
Managed to catch the start of the stream.
Been a while.
Welcome.
Good to have you.
Great starting a new game?
Yeah, I'm gonna start a new game, man.
It's gonna be good.
I'm in a fantastic mood today, man.
I can't wait to play some more Noiter.
And I'm still on my no coke streak, okay?
No can today.
I'm drinking sparkling water from a big two liter container.
That's my closest thing to coke that I got right now.
Without it being coke.
I still have nightmares from my dentist telling me I should lay off coke.
So I'm doing it.
I'm doing it.
We're gonna fuck with Stavati more today?
Oh, you mean Stuart?
Oh, maybe.
I mean, I have a solid plan in place regarding that guy, by the way.
And the plan is we don't fuck with him.
We leave him alone until we're strong enough.
And then we fuck with him.
Oh, and we're gonna fuck with him.
It's gonna be good.
Did you put sugar in your coffee?
No way, man.
I take it black.
Not that I have anything against people who do that.
That's totally fine.
Trust me, I am one of the few very sugar addicted people.
So I understand.
You're making chicken stew with rice.
Mr. Beat, you always make something super awesome, it seems.
I applaud you for your cooking skills.
Good going.
I never drink coke.
Good on you, Frank.
Good on you, man.
Subnautica, probably one of my favorite terror games.
Nothing is more scarier than exploring big places with low visibility.
There is something scary about the open ocean, isn't there?
And the depths.
And the fact that when you look somewhere, it's just darkness.
That shit is hella unnerving.
Okay.
For real?
I'm still on the planet, even though I don't have to be since I love the world too much.
Yeah, that's awesome.
The world is indeed amazing just to swim around and explore everything.
It's so much fun.
They're making a new subnautica as well.
I can't wait, dude.
The lassophobia is real.
That's right.
That's the word for that.
I don't have that, I don't think, but imagine playing that game with the lassophobia.
That sounds crazy.
How would you rate Noita as a single player game?
You mean as opposed to a multiplayer game?
Because it's only a single player game.
I mean, I know there's mods for multiplayer, people have told me.
I lied.
But I mean, as a single player game, aka as a game, it's pretty fucking high up there.
So far, I would say close to 10 out of 10 for me.
And I'm not even done.
I mean, this is just the perfect roguelike in my mind.
It makes you want to go again and again and again.
And you get frustrated at times, of course, because of your own inability to do simple things.
But man, is it just fun to go again.
And the fact that the game makes you want to go again is a testament to how good it is.
100 lalwan.
Yeah, I know.
People told me there's a multiplayer version.
Apparently, there's also a PvP version.
You managed to skip this game for years and finally started playing.
God run ongoing.
Nice.
I guess that just means you have a very good run going.
Speaking of roguelikes, would you play the upcoming Mugenics?
I haven't heard about that.
Game by the Binding of Isaac creator.
I think I think I want to play Binding of Isaac first, because I've only heard good things about it.
And it's one of those games that I think I will enjoy because I have such low expectations for it.
I don't know why, I just do.
So I can only get positively surprised, right?
I just found out about you.
I mean, how did you find out about me?
I'm actually curious.
I still can't believe people found my outer wilds back in the day.
It's what started all of this, basically.
It's so cool.
By Isaac when there's a sale for the DLCs in advance, otherwise it costs 60 euros or so.
Oh, that's a good tip.
I may just put it on my wish list on Steam.
Usually that gives me an update when it goes on sale.
Binding of Isaac one billion hours of gameplay incoming?
I mean, trust me, I love that.
The more the better.
I love games that grab you and make you want to play it forever.
And I know, like I've been that gamer, trust me.
I've played World of Warcraft Classic for thousands of hours.
I would play that...
I would say World of Warcraft, like the old school version, is the only game that I have ever been able to play for 12 hours straight every day, every day.
Like, it's insane what that game does.
It's so much fun.
I can keep going forever.
I took a year of my life not working.
I saved up money when World of Warcraft Classic came out.
I took a whole year out of my life just to play that game.
I shit you're not.
And back in the private server times, I was playing with one of the best guilds in the world and all that.
Well, then later on became known as Apes in the Classic.
Yeah, I went nuts, guys.
I'm a real gamer.
So I basically worked as a high school teacher for two years, saved up a bunch of money.
And then Classic was announced.
I was like, fuck this shit.
I'm taking everything off.
I'm going to play this game now.
Yeah, I went nuts.
You found it through the Minecraft stuff.
Okay.
Someone shared your Minecraft playthrough and I was like, hey, maybe he played some Nautica.
Okay, okay.
Yeah, the Minecraft stuff has been super popular as well.
I'm returning to Minecraft as well at some point, by the way.
I want to play hardcore.
I've been getting that Minecraft itch.
I'm not gonna lie.
I've been trying to scratch that itch a little bit playing with one of my friends, but super little.
Like we built a very simple house inside a cave.
We have our own server.
Have you played Totally Accurate Battle Simulator?
I have not, but I've heard about it.
It's kind of a meme game, right?
Whispers at the bus stop.
Found out about kids out in the schoolyard.
Found out about you.
I feel like that's a song you're trying to reference there or not.
I'm not quite sure.
In any case, that's... gap year only for a while.
That's crazy.
I know.
I'm fucked in the head.
What can I say?
I live and breathe games, dude.
Video games and movies?
My god, man.
You know how Hideo Kojima says his body is 70% movies?
I feel that way, but with video games and it's 90%.
So as good as Nautica is in any other single player game, there are so many good single player games.
I don't think I could play them for 12 hours straight every day, similar to World of Warcraft.
There's something about that game that hits me in the right spot.
I don't understand what it is.
I think it's the social aspect.
You know, you're hanging out with people at the same time in the game, playing with them.
It's like a second life almost.
That sounds totally no life.
You know what I mean.
Anyway, guys, it's time.
I'm gonna start a new run.
And you know what?
I feel so good today.
I predict no deaths today.
I can't say that without laughing.
Oh, that's gonna bite me in the ass, isn't it?
But I feel great, let me tell you.
I just need to, you know, get in there.
Oh, yeah.
Okay, I'm gonna have another sip here.
I had a no death stream before in Noisa, guys.
I think.
Yeah, I think I did.
I think I did.
And it was a long one, too.
Hopefully you can't hear my dishwasher in the background.
I once again foolishly turned it on right before the stream.
But I don't think any one of you have ever heard it.
So it's actually probably fine.
All right, you guys are being shut down.
No offense, as always.
I do actually want to do more of your interaction in the future with other games.
I feel like I am a little disconnected from you guys at times.
So we're gonna have to play some games where I can talk to you at the same time.
But of course, games where spoilers are a thing, I'm obviously gonna stick to my normal way of doing things here.
But you know, okay, let's see.
New game.
Hmm.
Not yet.
We're gonna try the daily run in the future.
I am curious about that.
Okay, it is night, and we have the magic missile.
That's a good start.
That means extra HP out the gate.
Hell yeah.
What the fuck is that?
What's happening here?
That's weird.
I think I've seen that before once.
But it's been a while.
All right, here we go.
Let's see if I can do this without looking.
You ready?
One.
Here we go.
Okay, one more.
There it is.
Oh my god.
Oh, that's amazing, dude.
Oh, let's be careful.
I have polymorphine on me and not water.
We gotta be really careful there.
In fact, I'm so careful, I'm gonna empty it immediately.
Because we don't want to take any chances with that shit.
Trust me.
Nope.
We should find a little, uh, something like this.
Can I... So I have bouncing burst.
That's not gonna dig anything.
But I can put some polymorphine somewhere, maybe over here.
Okay, damn it.
I thought maybe that would be a little hole of some sort.
I'm gonna have to dispose of that inside of, um, the hemisphere.
The good old hemisphere.
Do you want to make it?
Oh, you know what?
Actually...
That's perfect.
Ah, one more.
I know I'm wasting a little bit of ammo here, but I think it's for... I think it's for a good cause.
Look at this.
I'm never coming back down here.
There we go.
Just get rid of that stuff.
Pee a big pile.
Or pool, not pile.
I think pile is for countable objects.
Pool is for uncountable objects.
Think about that for a second.
And when you're done thinking about that, remember you're dead.
It is true without lying, certain and most true.
That which is below is like that which is above.
And that which is above is like that which is below.
To do the miracles of only one thing.
And as all things have been and arose from one by the meditation of one, mediation of one.
So all things have their birth from this one thing by adaptation.
Is that telling me that...
That's like a slight hint that there's stuff up in the sky, right?
But that is almost saying that the stuff up in the sky is the same as the stuff down below.
Which is not really the case in my experience.
But who knows?
Very interesting lore there.
That needs to be studied.
We need to find water actually.
Water is essential to survival.
Now, imagine if I was graced with 10 hearts in the hemisphere.
How crazy... I wonder if that's even possible.
I do wonder what the limits are for extreme RNG in this game, you know?
Like, could that even happen?
Sounds insane.
There's probably an upper limit to how many there...
There can spawn in a given area or like volume or area of locations.
Kill that guy.
Actually, this is a pretty good one.
It's shooting fast and yeah, not bad.
Not bad.
Is there something in there?
I really got to find water.
Otherwise, I can't turn the toxic shit into non-toxic shit.
Oh my god, sludge everywhere.
That is not what you want to see.
Actually, there's a bit of water here.
So here's the thing.
We only need a sliver of water.
Hold on, there was some more water up here too.
Can we maybe grab some?
Oh yeah, look at this, look at this.
Sliver of water is all I need to make infinite water.
I put it in the wrong spot.
Okay, you know, I'm gonna find water somewhere else.
But I should have put it in the big pool.
I thought maybe it would slide down and make it water from there.
Okay, slime potion?
What is this stuff, man?
I don't want that.
Ah, shit's on fire, yo.
Oh, is that water?
It sure is.
So watch.
Infinite water!
That's how you do it.
Now we can spread this everywhere.
And make the hemisphere great again.
Oh, man.
And there we go.
Give me water.
Perfect.
That's a good start.
What's that?
Silver pouch.
I'll take it, I'll take it.
I wonder if I can turn the silver into gold somehow.
Or trade it somehow with someone.
I wonder if trading is a thing.
Similar to some other game I'm thinking of right now.
I don't want to spoil anything, of course, for anybody.
But those that know know.
Bro, there's a severe lack of water in this hemisphere.
This is wild.
It's all toxic sludge.
It's always been.
Oh, hold on.
There we go.
I think this is more like swamp.
Yeah, that's fine, though.
Swamp is okay.
Okay, grab it all.
And we're full.
And I even have my... You know what?
I'm gonna put this on my tablet keybind.
The deadly weapon.
Boing.
By the way, I have a new idea regarding a steward.
I'm basically gonna perform... Oh, I need to pick this up again.
It involves the tablet here.
I'm basically gonna do this.
Watch.
I'm gonna put it down like this.
So all of this is momentum, right?
So if this is like the path down to him, I'm gonna practice a little bit to always get the consistent throw.
So like, bam.
You know?
Didn't need to break that.
But I need to practice the consistent throw, basically, is what I'm saying.
And when I can do that, and I can throw it with enough speed, maybe it'll be enough to one-shot him.
Because if I miss him, you know, that's bad.
You take a shot at the king, you better not miss.
How do I... Can I really not?
Okay, fine.
Dang it.
That's annoying.
Oh, there we go!
Good start, good start.
Beautiful stuff.
Hey, guy, come here.
Jesus!
I didn't mean to do that.
Okay, never mind.
Terrible start, terrible start.
Not a good start.
I'll take it back.
I was aiming for the other explosive, and somehow I fucked that up.
That was a huge mistake.
This game is very unforgiving at times.
But it is my fault.
I did an oopsie.
Okay, slowly exploring everything here.
Grab some more water.
This is the nastiest swamp water I've ever had.
Also, that is mostly peat, it seems.
I got a shotgun, dude.
Oh, no.
A couple barneys.
That was pretty good.
Levitation.
That's actually...
You know what?
I have an idea.
I have a fucking idea here.
Oh, I don't have no more.
I guess I get rid of the slime.
I'm gonna go on top of the tree, and I'm gonna get that music wand.
Because the wand itself, if I remember correctly, is not actually that bad, right?
Maybe that's a good thing to get.
Like, if I get levitation where I can actually...
Oh, but wait a minute.
I need some digging.
I need digging to be able to do that.
Because, yeah, hold on.
I need digging.
Because I need to get into the room.
Maybe what I have is enough.
Depends what I'll find.
But yeah.
Look, it is finally some clean water.
That's what I'm talking about.
For the first time, we find the good stuff.
And now I contaminated it again.
I do remember there was one drawback to that music wand.
I don't quite remember what it was.
There was one very important thing where it really sucked.
Bone.
Dude, I have an idea, by the way.
Remember the bone skull in the desert?
There's like a huge eye hole, right?
Maybe if we put bone in there and fill it up with bone or just one bone.
You know, maybe something will happen.
What's this?
Hey, not bad.
And the wand itself is pretty good too.
Very sweet.
Hey, okay, he's down.
That's good.
Now we have a shotty.
Get that.
Get the money.
Wow, hold on.
The acid burns through the brickwork.
That's kind of a big deal.
I mean, I guess I knew that already, but I can use that to my advantage, I guess.
You know what?
If I find a sea of acid or whatever it's called, I'm gonna try some stuff with that.
Hell yeah.
Oh, someone used the wand here.
That is sketchy.
I understand why that wand was lying on the floor there and not in the hands of somebody.
They killed themselves with it.
That's a clear identifier that you shouldn't do that.
Oh my god.
He actually hit me.
I'm low on hp here.
It's getting a little scary.
There's a himis.
Two himis, one himis, two himis, three himis.
Go lots of fun.
Slow the flow.
What's that?
Another silver pouch?
Watch the man.
All right.
What's that?
Ambrosia, dude.
Fuck the silver.
We getting ambrosia, baby.
I need to play this super safe right now because I'm so low.
I do want to get to that wand.
Uh-oh.
Oh, that's bad.
That's just real bad.
What happens if I put uh a circle of stillness?
That is actually big.
Oh, I may take that.
Yeah, definitely.
And we can use that against the the guy on the left.
Dude, circle of stillness into tablet throw.
Oh, that's sick.
That's sick.
Right?
That's like foolproof almost.
If I hit him, of course.
Oh, he's burning everything.
That's not good.
I'm scared, dude, with this little hp here.
Also, I saw a shotty man.
I am tempted to just go through the portal at this point.
Also, I'm more comfortable with this being here.
Three is stillness.
Okay.
Ooh, pheromone.
That's also super nice.
You know what?
Maybe I'll exchange this levitation for now, because I don't think I have the digging capabilities.
Even with this, I don't think I can get through the tree.
Tree is like super hard.
Like very dense material.
Oh, not the collapsed mines.
That's a bit too dangerous, I think.
I'm gonna go this way instead.
What's up here?
I always want to check if there's something in the liquid.
Usually, hearts are hiding there, you know?
Maybe even in these.
Hold on.
Okay, never mind.
I feel like I've seen a heart in one of those before.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Motherfucker!
How?
Come on.
That's right.
That's right, bitch!
There it is!
Okay, I think we're about to leave.
With this amount of HP, we can't stay here.
Also, I see fire on the floor.
It's bad.
We're leaving.
Yep.
Play it safe.
So, here's the thing.
If we can't find anything in this spot right here that will for sure kill Stuart, we leave him alone.
Now, that is sweet.
Mmm, okay.
All right.
And wands.
What's that?
High mana, low capacity, phasing.
Projectiles seemingly phase through you.
You know what?
We're gonna try new things today.
Why not?
Let's try this.
Let's see what the fuck happens.
Are the projectiles gonna actually hurt me or not?
Am I immune to enemy ranged attacks?
That almost seems too good to be true, right?
But I'll try it.
So, here's the thing.
This is the one I want to try.
I forgot my tablet's unreal!
Fuck.
Okay, never mind.
I guess we're not killing Stuart.
So, of all the things I have here, I should probably take this.
Let me see the wands.
Whoa, that's a lot of mana.
0.25, 0.45.
Oh, that's good, except it's shuffle.
That's also shuffle, but it's good.
Actually, not bad.
If I can find the... Wow, look at the castellae on this.
That is super low.
Oh, but the mana charge speed is actually okay.
What, it shoots two spells per cast?
This could be really sick if you had a bunch of the same, right?
But recharge time is terrible.
So, actually, it's terrible.
This one is nice.
And I have a newfound appreciation for these.
The bubble sparks.
I do like the bubble sparks.
Let's see this.
Okay.
0.43.
Here's the question.
Do these things hurt me now?
Do they face through me?
I'm testing.
Oh, wait.
Oh, fuck.
Why am I so scared of that?
I don't understand why my body is having such a violent reaction.
Okay, so projectiles do not seem to undamage me, unfortunately.
I still take damage.
That's a bummer.
But maybe it's because it's a physical one.
It's hard to say.
0.23.
This one is 0.25.
We could utilize this.
Hold on.
If we do something like...
Not bad.
Not bad at all.
That's pretty dope, huh?
Hold on.
These actually reduce cast-a-lay.
If I could find a one with a low recharge and high cast-a-lay, I could potentially use it.
To good effect.
I also need to buy this one.
Obviously.
We need these.
That's a must.
Let's get a light as well.
Fire trail.
Maybe one more of these.
Let's see how that looks.
Okay.
Not super intrigued.
Do five damage.
So I'm thinking this.
Uh...
Look at that.
It's gonna shoot one of these in a random direction.
I don't care about it, but it's gonna affect the rest in a nice way.
Let's just see the difference.
Oh, yeah, it's definitely better.
That's sick.
Yeah.
Is there a big difference though?
I think there is.
Yeah, it's faster.
Super cool.
We're definitely gonna have a black hole wand.
It's gonna be shuffled.
It doesn't matter.
Although this one is...
Having a disc projectile wand would maybe be better.
Like it's solid.
It does a lot of damage.
It's not bad.
Oh wait, that's a bad idea maybe.
Yeah, don't do that.
That's bad.
You could experiment with that, I guess.
Maybe a bit too d... Let's try that.
Let's try and rock that for a bit.
Let me get rid of these.
Uh, can I actually... No, okay.
This is good, I think.
I like it.
I also have to remember, if I can find...
What's that spell called?
Energy sphere.
It actually does decent digging.
That's the thing.
Also, there's rocks here.
I have to remember that.
69 gold.
Nice.
Let's go.
We're not fighting Stuart.
Or are we?
No, we're not.
Oh, wait a minute.
I almost want to try circle of stillness on him.
I have a feeling though, that he's not gonna be affected by it.
Even if he is gonna get frozen, I can't really kill him is what I'm thinking here.
Yeah, I'm gonna not take the chance.
When we have the power, that's when we leave.
Get rid of all that lava.
Oh man, the orcs is very...
big on this.
It does good damage.
Oh man, these guys are super dangerous.
The amount of lava they dispel is insane.
Or not dispel, expel.
Dude, my screen is shaking hardcore.
Something is exploding somewhere.
Wait, I do 50 damage?
No way.
Does the fire add that much?
That's insane.
Hey, look at that.
That's fantastic.
And the wand is also insane.
0.05?
That's really good for like something simple like a disc projectile.
Not bad at all.
Let's grab some more water.
And put this here.
And we have that, that, that seems good to me.
Very nice.
Okay.
I'm a bit nervous about, um, having burning trail on this.
I feel like it's gonna fuck me over at some point, you know?
It's gonna bite me in the old ass.
Oh, is this just a normal teleport?
Oh, it is.
Okay, it's not short.
That's not preferable.
Ah, but that is very preferable.
Look at that.
I'm a fat cat.
I'm gonna use my black hole.
Why not?
Are you kidding?
I hate that.
That's so unfortunate.
Okay, he's gone.
Okay, I still do 20 damage, it seems.
Maybe some enemies are more, I mean, less resistant to fire, of course, and maybe that's what did it.
Got him.
Let's go for a swim.
Man, even the teleport bolt is being, like, slowed down in water.
That's kind of funny to me.
Whoa.
Fat cat.
I've been there already.
I can burn the stuff with my...
Yeah, that's set of fire now.
I wonder if you can say set a fire.
It's more like set a blaze or set on fire.
I don't think you can say set a fire.
I think some acid fell here.
It is hard to hit with this weapon, for sure.
But the damage is solid.
What is this doing again?
I haven't even felt this at all.
I feel like it's...
a little bit weird.
Face through me, huh?
Whoop, that was scary.
That blade almost hit me.
I'm playing it pretty safe here.
I think I'm doing good.
This is a solid coal pit so far.
Ah, a chest, my lord.
No!
Aww.
Oh well.
That's okay.
Okay.
I think the thing I want most from those chests is health.
Give me a heart and I'll be happy.
There's something up there.
I have a feeling.
Or not.
Sweet.
The reason I'm using that black hole so liberally is because I'm gonna start using those spell refreshers more.
I feel like I'm saving them too much.
You know?
I need to not save them that much.
I need to actually use my spells.
First priority in this game is surviving, man.
And exploring.
That's gonna be my new philosophy.
Don't be afraid to use the spells.
Ah, the shotgun guy.
One down.
There we go.
Another one!
Nice!
And wood I can burn through.
Only can set that a fire.
Come on.
Okay, that's burning.
That's perfect.
I'm gonna get in there.
I got a hoodlum!
Oh, motherfucker.
That was a full-on hit there.
Had way more HP than I anticipated.
Wow, another full-on hit right into the lava.
This is going fantastic, huh?
What a series of events.
Can I at least get in here now?
Thanks.
Well, there we go!
But this one is so good, though.
I don't know what to replace.
Maybe this one.
Ah, the circle of stillness is incredible, though.
Ah, man.
I'm gonna replace it.
I want the small teleport.
Much better.
Burned through.
Okay.
Whoa!
Okay, portal is there.
We have an out.
Whoa!
Thank God you can hear their loading of the shotgun.
Otherwise, those guys would be incredibly annoying.
I mean, they still are, you know?
But imagine if they didn't make a sound.
Sweet.
Whoa!
Be careful.
What have we
got here?
Okay, I'm gonna burn through here.
Like, fire's okay, you know?
It's a decent at getting through stuff like this.
I could use a black hole, but...
In this case, I'm just gonna burn my way through.
Oh, hello.
Ran out.
Okay.
That was close.
That was dumb luck there.
Whoa!
Whoop!
It's getting a little dangerous.
What the fuck?
That guy's stuck in the brickwork.
Weird.
Sucks to be him.
Come here.
Sometimes, yeah, I gotta get out of the way when I shoot enemies too, because my projectile comes back because it bounces off of them.
Or it hits them and then it sort of falls to the ground after when they're dead.
It gets a little sketchy.
Oh, there's a chest!
Ma, dude.
Oh, this guy has a lot of HP.
We gotta be careful.
And this is the guy that throws potions.
Hold on.
Uh...
Hmm.
I was trying to think, could we maybe farm those if there was some water nearby, but there isn't, so...
Rip!
He died?!
How?
Did the chest hit him?
Oh, what happened there?
Wait, why doesn't that...
Hmm.
What?!
No way!
We can dig!
Fuck yeah, man!
Yo, that's fucking awesome!
So weird.
That was just in there, huh?
Cool.
Wait, can I dig through anything?
What about...
Gray... okay, Gray Rock is a no-go, unfortunately.
But that's fine.
I mean, this is super helpful.
We have a little digging.
If I see some coal and there's gold, easy money.
Uh... get some more water.
Kinda want to go through.
450.
Hmm, yeah, let's go.
Ooh.
Let's do it.
Hit the HP.
What do we got?
Oh, I like what I'm seeing here.
So far, so good.
What's that?
Wandex... ooh, but this one.
Ooh, we gotta go with that.
We gotta go with the perk lottery.
Gotta play the lottery.
Give me that.
Chunk of soil.
What is... hold on.
What is this?
Don't solve yourself.
We gotta try this again.
I am actually intrigued about this.
Right.
Uh-oh.
There we go.
It's just a bunch of soil.
I'm gonna get rid of it.
Bunch of so... ooh, we also have a digging mechanism.
And that is... dropper bolt.
Critical on oiled enemies.
Not bad, I guess.
Okay, so we don't want this.
Normal teleport can go away.
In fact, I should put stuff I don't want into the water.
I think it's...
more appropriate.
Now, this wand right here is actually sick.
Like, imagine...
Well, even this.
Oh, wait a minute.
Uh, we need... we need...
Oh, if only we could reduce recharge on this.
That would be sick.
But we have a mana now.
And that is big.
We have mana.
How can I abuse that?
I need a spell that costs a lot of mana.
To take advantage of that.
I don't really have anything like that.
But, if I have a wand that has a shitty mana recharge.
Like this one.
It's shuffled, but...
Maybe that's fine.
Let me put this here for now.
Like, if this is in here somewhere, it's maybe gonna be enough, you know?
It's just gonna trigger once in a while and that should be fine.
Oh, but hold on, the castile is terrible.
Why would I do that?
0.17.
Yeah, I'm not sure why I would do that.
Yeah, I don't know.
0.33, 0.45, 0.65, 0.3.
I don't really have any good wands, I feel like.
Like, I...
What can I make, man?
Oh, wait, I have this one.
That reduces recharge.
Hold up, hold up a second, hold up a second, I have an idea.
We're gonna be doing, uh, watch this.
We're gonna use this on a dummy spell, okay?
So, we're gonna do something like that onto this.
Well, is that working as I think?
Reduces...
Hmm, it's not really doing what I thought it would do.
Yeah, look, now it's actually working.
That's weird, what if I do that?
No, that's weird.
Okay, this actually reduces recharge time too.
It costs zero mana?
Wait, what?
This costs zero mana.
Isn't that super weird?
So, it reduces by 0.17 if I do this.
Oh, there it is!
I think this is faster.
Oh, yeah, look at that.
That's it, boys.
That's the digging.
The digging is there.
We got it.
And now, we need to make an actual damage wand.
Something that isn't shit.
I think I have to go with the disc projectile.
And make something out of it.
It's just the really good damage I have, you know.
Everything else kind of sucks.
Hmm.
I mean, we don't need all of these, I guess.
Let's put them here.
A neat pile.
Okay.
And then...
We could maybe...
Can I apply this to some dummy spell?
What if I apply it to an empty spell?
Oh, wait.
That's...
Oh, hold on.
I don't have mana for that, anyway.
But imagine.
Just apply it to an empty spell.
That's a bad idea.
No, don't do that.
Don't do that.
That's bad.
Definitely one... Oh, I should take one of these, of course.
Mall teleport.
Yes.
0.25.
0.65.
I need the lowest.
This one is actually better, I think.
Right?
Dum-dum.
Why is that slower?
That's weird.
Okay.
I think I'm gonna go with that.
And maybe a chunk of soil.
What is this point of this?
Oh, you can block paths off, I guess.
If someone is following you, just block off the path.
They can't get to you.
That wouldn't be too bad.
You know, like block off one side, if you're in a tight corridor or something.
I see a use for that there.
Or maybe if you put this into liquids, something will happen.
Hold on, actually.
Let's try that.
I made a... I soiled myself.
A mountain of soil.
That's... It became mud!
All right.
I don't really see the use, I gotta be honest.
All right, let's put our black holes down.
I could even... So, do I have the capability of killing this guy now?
I still don't think I do.
I don't.
Not that I can see.
Although...
Ambrosia, maybe we can make something happen with that.
But they would... I would have to make like a little pool of it somewhere.
Oh, wait a minute.
How do I... How would I do that?
If... Okay, if I could empty this of water, fill it with Ambrosia, stand at the bottom.
He's gonna come down, right?
Hopefully, and not just stand up here.
And maybe if he's close enough, I go...
on his face.
You know?
Think about that.
Or...
We make a pool behind the statue here.
Hold on, let's just quickly try it.
Does that make sense?
Does that work?
It does work.
But I gotta be careful, because this will presumably destroy the statue.
Yeah, so if he comes here and we stand in the pool, we go...
Right?
That could work.
Guys, I think I'm gonna try it.
I know we have sick perks.
Perk Lottery is amazing, but I gotta experiment here.
Let's see if this works.
We're probably gonna die.
Oh, hold on.
Let me fill it up.
I'm gonna fill it up.
The reason I'm doing it here is because there's such a little space here.
I don't want to risk him hovering 10 meters above me, and then I'm trapped below.
I need him to get close.
You know?
Very close.
Oh, unless him shooting his spells will knock this statue around and...
All this ambrosia will go everywhere, but I guess I could make a pool here.
In fact, I'm just gonna empty my ambrosia.
Better safe than sorry, right?
Better safe than sorry, boy.
That's what I say.
Oh, yeah, look at this.
We're gonna make it so safe.
Oh, if only I had a long-distance cast, that would be crazy.
Ah, let's see.
What else do I have that could potentially help us here?
I guess we do have small teleport bolt.
We could, uh, get the fuck out of dodge quick if we can't kill him.
Okay, that's the backup.
That's the backup.
If shit hits the fan, we leave.
And before it, I may buy some stuff on the way out.
Buy that for later.
Yep.
Okay, that seems good.
I also got to take a mean piss, but I will do that after.
I'm gonna use this energy that I have in me right now.
Uh, I'm not gonna stand over here.
I am gonna throw a black hole in some direction here.
In fact, I may just throw it down.
Do it!
All right, dude, you're angry now.
I know you are.
Oh!
Fucking physiological reactions.
Uh, just to be sure, this thing will...
not go through your shield, right?
It will not.
Okay, good.
Good, good, good.
Come here.
So if I just hover here and I go... Oh, I hope he comes close enough.
This is it!
Okay, he doesn't destroy the statue.
My ambrosia!
Oh no!
He's destroying my ambrosia!
Okay, we're leaving, we're leaving, we're leaving, we're leaving, we're leaving, we're leaving.
Nope, no, no, no, we're leaving.
We are getting the fuck out of here, bro.
Hopefully he won't follow me all the way down here.
Okay, so he can...
Oh my god, guys!
Holy shit!
Calm down, guys!
Wait, that guy shoots arrows?
Who's shooting arrows?
Oh god!
Okay, at least Stuart is not following us.
That's actually big news.
That's actually really big.
Oh, he has a wand.
Oh, that's the guy with the arrows.
I see.
Oh, you bastard.
Come here.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Did you die?
I got you.
Damn!
Holy arrow!
All right.
Okay, that's actually really big.
If we have teleport, we can always get away.
Safely, I mean.
Worst case scenario, we just leave.
That's actually great to know.
So Ambrosia is a no-go.
Unless I can get it in a position where I... Oh my god, this guy keeps hitting me.
Where I can easily hit him with the close-quarter stuff.
Right?
Because I think the drill would have killed him if I got in range.
Actually, hold on.
I think I could have done it, guys.
Because...
Ambrosia has like a... it has like a lingering effect.
It still works on you when you're in the air after you've been in it for like a little short while.
Maybe I could have gone up, quickly down.
Uh, Ambrosia up again, and then up, and then down again.
I think that... actually, that's... I should have thought about that.
Ah!
I was stuck!
Damn it, man.
But look at this digging.
The digging is nuts, guys.
This is the realest dig in a while.
That's so real.
What's that?
Freezing liquid.
Okay.
Ooh.
Don't come here.
Explode.
Come on.
I don't know where it is now.
Look at him chopping up his friend immediately.
No remorse.
Doesn't even care.
By the way, I made a backup of my entire save folder.
Just in case something would be corrupted from the crash.
Or potential crashes in the future.
Oh wait, these guys are gonna be impossible to kill with my disc projectile.
Unless I can come from below and say hallelujah.
Oh shit!
Oh, it's bad.
I have really shitty ones, guys.
This is not looking good.
I gotta find something better.
That's a trap.
Oh man.
Oh yeah.
Ukuskivi.
Nope.
Nightmares I have of the ukuskivi.
All right.
Okay, let it be something good.
Yo.
That's not bad, I guess.
But I don't really need it because I have insane digging.
So we're fine.
Another wand!
Dude.
I'm being spoiled.
Ooh, that's tempting.
That's tempting.
That's... that's...
Hold on.
Ball lightning, summon three, short range.
I don't remember how this works.
Is it gonna kill me?
It's not!
Okay, okay, perfect.
It's not.
Uh, I may just use it.
This is a run of experimentation.
Also, I'm gonna change my wand whenever I don't need it.
So I don't mess it up.
Oh wait, that's not doing shit.
Hold on, we're going back.
No, no, no, that sucks.
That's bad.
At least for now.
Maybe I'll try again in the future, but uh, for now, I was not intrigued by that and I can't risk anything right now with such low HP.
Oh, come
on, kill it, kill it, kill it.
Thank you.
That was really well handled.
Now we collect our paycheck.
And another wand.
Nice.
I have nightmares about digging into water, by the way, because of the Ukuskivi incident.
Dude, this game is just throwing teleports at me, huh?
Hmm, whoop, there we go.
Dude, I need vampirism now because I have this ultimate digger that will also destroy corpses.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, I hit myself, I hit myself.
The mistakes were made.
Wait, the snipers are hunting these guys too.
I guess the Heezy people hate them as much as everyone else.
Some bombs?
Nah, although...
Hmm, nah.
The wand was okay, but the spells were not.
Okay, take it easy.
I think it's time to find a portal again.
Shit.
Yeah, let's just dig down.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
That could have been bad.
Sweet, turn it into water.
What do we got here?
Critical plus?
Wow, that's just a straight up crit chance.
That's not bad.
That's actually pretty sick.
And the wand is also, well, a large recharge time.
That's the bummer there.
But wow, holy mana charge speed.
You know, maybe there's something we can do with that wand.
That's not too terrible.
But what would I replace?
I don't really have any damage.
Unless I take replace this now.
And I immediately go for the mountain.
Oh, that's a tough one, man.
I could also replace these, even though it feels like a crime.
Nah, let's leave this.
Let's leave it.
It's not incredible.
Like, it's definitely good, but it's not like mind-blowingly good.
Okay, the holy mountain is here.
Oh, hold on.
I don't want to tangle with that.
I'm gonna go through.
We have way too low HP.
We gotta make a good wand here.
Man, come on.
Could have left it, I guess.
Oh, oh no, I forgot.
What?
Uh, shit, guys.
We're leaving.
Is he coming?
Oh, my God.
Oh, no.
Hey, but the good news is this mountain is still in...
Holy shit.
Guys, I think this is the end.
This is looking real bad.
Okay, you know what?
I have an idea, I have an idea, I have an idea.
Come here.
Come here, fucker.
Oh, okay, okay, okay.
Wait, are they fighting him?
Back up, back up, back up.
Uh, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
I'm gonna use this time, use this time to get this.
Look, what kind of perks we have?
What kind of perks?
I mean, sure, I guess.
Why not?
Um, what would be able to kill this guy?
What's that?
Water to poison, yikes.
Nope, that's not good, that's not good, that's not good.
What if I...
If he comes from below and I shoot a rock from up here, it's gonna have enough momentum to maybe penetrate his shit.
Come here.
Oh, dude.
Oh, no, it penetrates.
Oh, I have no more.
Uh, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit.
Hold on, I can deflect.
I cannot deflect, never mind, never mind.
Uh, hold on, hold on.
Let me think about...
What?
Why did that shoot at such a speed?
The fuck is going on here?
Huh?
Oh, no, I have no real weapon.
We gotta go back down.
Wait, come here.
Come here, fucker!
You're gonna die now!
What I'm talking about!
Oh, yeah, baby!
That was crazy, man!
Fuck, yeah.
Oh, my God.
Oh, that's what I'm talking about.
Oh, yeah!
Uh-oh.
Hold on.
Uh, switch, uh, give me this guy right, I guess.
Oh, this is... I'm not gonna kill that guy.
I'm not gonna kill that guy.
Right!
Maybe kill him with this?
I don't have enough money.
Yeah, we're out of here.
We gotta go on an expedition to find some...
I need to get my disc projectile back, I think.
That's the only real way.
Triplicate bolt, triplicate bolt.
That is the solution.
Oh, I'm catching myself in the corner here.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Let's be careful here.
Let's plan our strategy.
If this guy's gonna come close, I'm gonna saw him in half.
That's right.
That's how we do it.
Come here.
I'm gonna take him out one by one.
There we go.
Okay, we're low on HP.
That's really bad.
He's gonna throw dynamite at me.
Nice.
This is a real melee run.
Okay, okay, okay.
Now we leave.
Did they leave my home?
They did not.
Whoops, didn't mean to do that.
Oh, that's fine, that's fine, that's fine.
Switch this one.
Whoa, fuck me, dude.
Dude, I do no damage.
This is rip.
I have no damage, dude.
Well, I have 300 monies now.
Maybe I can buy that glowing lance.
Okay, this is the plan.
Got him!
What a, what a, what a, what a!
Oh, fuck.
Oh, that sucks.
That sucks.
Ah, that was a shit, shit show of a run anyway.
I'm kind of happy that one is over.
Move on to a new one, man.
But that was fun.
So if I have a digging bolt, I can kill Stuart.
And I can do it in a good way.
I just need to get him to come around the corner, and then I fuck him.
Yeah, that's gonna be good.
By the way, I think I realized why the black hole went so fast.
I think it has to do with my projectile repulsion field in front of me.
You know how it pushes away projectiles?
I think it acts sort of like an inverter when I shoot things away from me in the same direction as the field.
It gets accelerated.
Because it's like, instead of a projectile coming towards me being blown away, I already have some momentum in the direction away from me, and then it's getting amplified by the blowing away effect of that field.
Okay, I'm gonna take a quick piss and I'll be back.
All right, I'm back.
So I learned some good stuff.
Ambrosia is maybe a go-go if I can quickly jump up while I have the residual ambrosia on me.
And then I can mess with him.
That's one way to do it.
But I would need something that does a high amount of DPS.
For example, the drill I had.
Right?
Holy sh- Holy...
Wands.
Everywhere.
The air feels heavy?
Wait, what does that mean?
The air feels heavy.
What does that mean?
Ooh.
Yo!
How's that for a wand?
That could be a potential digging wand.
If we find another bolt...
What's happening over here?
Dude, wands everywhere.
0.07.
That's quite fast.
And it has a lot- You know what?
It's just better than this, I think.
Straight up.
Oh, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Let me see.
Oh yeah, that's the shotgun there.
But there's a large recharge, but that's fine.
I don't care about that.
And I have water.
Amazing.
This is a great start, guys.
Let's blow this up.
Nice.
Actually, I'm not sure it is better.
I think it will be really nice if I can put in something that reduces recharge time.
But for now, it's okay.
It's gonna do one, two, three, four, five of these times three.
That's like 15 damage in one shot.
It's pretty dope, I think.
It's not bad.
Oh, there's a chest.
Ooh.
Dude, that duel with Stuart was actually amazing.
That was really fun.
I'm not gonna lie, that shit was entertaining for me.
I feel like I'm getting to know his attacks more and the way he moves around, you know?
Like I can...
And now that I know, I can just fucking leave.
And he's maybe gonna follow me if I'm not fast enough.
That's one thing.
But I realize all these things, right?
It's knowledge.
Knowledge in the knowledge bank.
It's gonna serve me well in the future.
Man, what is this shit?
I guess I'll use a bomb, huh?
But, ah, that's annoying.
I'm gonna use a bomb over here instead.
Or...
Hold on, I have an idea, I have an idea.
Look at that!
Galaxy brain.
That's gonna burn through.
And then I have access.
Hopefully the...
Why is it burning so slow?
All right, I'm gonna come back to you.
You can burn away.
At some point, that shit's gonna burn all the way through and we're gonna be home free.
What do we got over here?
Ooh.
It's him, his town.
What's that?
Is that berserkium?
Hold on.
Whiskey.
I don't know about that.
Oh, wait, I am fully drunk right now.
Did you see my shots?
Flammoxium.
Nah.
Oh, god damn it.
Acid.
What if it...
Dude, these potions suck.
They're all bad for me.
Whiskey's bad for you.
Acid is bad for you.
Flammoxium is...
What's next, lava?
Another...
No.
Or...
Yeah, why not?
Get flummoxed.
I wonder what that means for enemies when they're flummoxed.
Maybe they're just unable to attack.
Maybe we should experiment with that.
For some reason, I read that as extreme holy mountain.
I don't know why.
I just thought extreme version of the holy mountain.
This is so holy.
You don't even know, bro.
So holy.
What's that?
Levitation.
Where did that come from?
You know what?
Actually, this acid potion...
could come in handy.
Because that shit cuts through brickwork.
And I can maybe even throw it on an enemy.
And that's gonna be entertaining.
Don't even think about it.
Okay.
In Visciblium, I would like that.
So I'm gonna actually blow my way through, I think.
Yep.
Sweet.
Thank you.
Dude, all we need now is the tablet and we can go on a sneaking ninja mission.
Remember that one time?
That was so much fun.
I fucking saw that one happen.
Like, I had a vision.
I was like, if I stand on this, shit's gonna go wrong, right?
It's gonna go wrong.
Sure enough.
I was debating kicking that shit to the left.
But then I saw the oil and I thought, nah, I don't want oil on me.
I'm gonna take a chance and stand on this and I immediately got executed for it.
No more thinking like that.
God damn it.
It's a classic.
That guy.
Let's go up here.
You there.
Oh, we're already at the edge.
We don't have any means of seeing things though.
That is unfortunate.
I want to see what's up here.
Okay, that's a dead end.
I think we may have to head out.
That guy just killed him?
No, he didn't die yet.
I thought he died.
Now he died.
I'm gonna water myself and pick up the gold.
Wait, where'd the gold go?
I think it somehow slipped into the coal.
That's my guess.
No, we're not leaving yet.
I need the tablet.
For sure.
And a bit a bit more money.
That's my wand.
See that he was flummoxed.
Oh my god.
There we go.
Thank you.
The game throws me a bone and I gladly eat it.
Nothing over here.
Except money.
This is a very relaxing hemisphere.
I'm enjoying this hemisphere.
This is good.
Oh my god.
Okay.
Where's my tablet, bitch?
Oh, that was a bit close.
That could have gone wrong.
Is that a long distance cast I spot with my eye?
What the hell is going on here?
What?
Huh?
Wait, what?
Why is that just hanging out here?
That spell was free too.
I don't understand what's going on.
What the fuck?
Oh my god.
Dude, this is nuts.
Is that...
Energy?
Oh my god, guys.
This is insanity.
Wait.
There's a worm somewhere.
There's a worm.
Salt?
Huh?
I've never seen that.
We gotta experiment with that.
Ambrosia.
Oh my lord.
Get rid of the whiskey.
Don't you break my ambrosia.
I will fucking tear off your limbs and play the drums with them.
Uh-oh.
Ooh, sweet.
That was a sniper shot.
Coot-a-grah.
This is a very interesting hemisphere, I gotta say.
Very interesting.
And we have a good spell already.
Chain Bolt, we're already set.
Like, Coldpits is already taken care of.
We just need to not die right now.
Of course, easier set than done.
Uh, where do I go?
I guess I have bombs.
Let's bomb.
I can't bomb that though, but I can bomb the Lomi right here.
Not bad!
I'm blowing up everything.
Look at that, we mixed it mid-air.
Heh heh heh.
That's kind of fun.
And now all that that's gonna drip down is gonna become water.
Give me water.
This is a very intriguing hemisphere, guys.
I am fucking hype.
I've never seen anything like this.
Now, I'm not one to look a gift horse in the mouth, but...
Maybe I can have another heart?
Maybe.
Just, oh no mas?
All right, it's tablet time.
Although,
um...
Dude!
Okay, dude, I have so many options.
I can...
This, this right here, guys, is pretty much what makes this run insane right now.
I can get out of every holy mountain.
And...
I don't need invi- I was thinking maybe I could use this to somehow get rid of, uh, Stuart.
But maybe I don't need to at all.
Unless, of course, that worm is causing issues somewhere and we may have to deal with them anyway.
So I think I have to prepare for that.
You know what?
I'll leave this pouch here.
Let's leave it right where we picked up this tablet.
I'm taking the tablet with me.
Yes, yes.
Also, what's this again?
Summon an autonomous rock ally.
You know- Wait, mana drain?
Maybe this is actually good against Stuart.
Who knows?
If he ends up popping up because of the worm, we're gonna try it.
And worst case, we're just leave, right?
Because we can teleport.
And GTFO.
So that's totally fine.
You only have 169 gold.
We definitely need more gold.
I mean, I spend a lot of it on those spells.
Of course, that's why I have so little.
But we can't go in there with that little amount of gold.
We gotta find a bit more.
I want to get down here.
I'm coming up.
I'm going up a little bit.
I'm gonna bottle it.
Okay.
Oh, hello.
It's tablet time.
Never mind.
Awesome.
Purifying powder plus coal plus moss.
Dude, I'm so conflicted.
Okay, you know what?
Leave this here.
I need to experiment with the purifying powder, man.
That is very interesting.
Kivaskivi?
Uh-oh.
I need to get not drunk.
If only you could take a bath in real life, huh?
And remove the hangover.
Wouldn't that be glorious?
Okay.
I want to find that worm and murder it.
It must be somewhere up here, right?
Because we have not gotten the message that the gods are angry.
So it has not dug all the way down.
The fuck is that?
Huh?
Worm meat?
That means it's dead.
I don't know why that's hanging out there.
That's a bit odd.
But this suggests to me that the worm died.
Oh, yeah, look.
More worm meat.
Fantastic.
Doop-doo.
Okay.
I think it's time to leave.
300 gold is actually not bad.
Yeah, let's go.
Just do it.
Grab this.
Before anything, I want to quickly make a wand that can...
do the teleporting.
Just in case I absolutely need it in a...
in a pinch.
19 mana charge?
That's probably fine for this.
Oh, we're so back.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, my God, that's insane.
Ooh, luminous drill!
All right.
Not too enticing stuff.
Let's see the perks.
Ooh.
I love this one!
We take that.
That's the best time to get it as well.
The earlier, the better.
This is fantastic.
This is absolutely fantastic.
This is my wand now.
The chain bolt is solid.
Can we make it better, though?
No, that sucks.
This wand seems really good for digging.
Yeah, it's gonna go up here.
Let's see.
We also have this, by the way.
That is a digger.
Remember?
That shit digs.
Good.
Yeah, we need three spells for that to work.
And I don't need all of these bouncing bursts.
In fact, I don't enjoy the bouncing burst very much.
Keep some of them.
You know what?
May as well keep them in case we absolutely need them.
Who knows?
I can always throw them away later.
No reason to throw them on the ground now.
Okay, so here's the thing.
Do we need any of these spells?
The double would be nice.
What about the wands themselves?
How good are they?
0.05.
Not like amazing.
I also want these luminous drills.
This costs 120.
190.
Oh, I can get them both.
Oh, yeah.
I'm doing it.
Get this one.
Get some light.
Double.
Very cool.
And this one is kind of shit.
We can do that.
Can we buy this?
Dude, this thing removes a lot of castellae.
It's actually kind of crazy.
Oh, I understand.
It shot the energy orb, which is a trigger.
So the next thing it happens when it collides with something is it shoots the luminous drill.
That is on a timer.
And then it shoots another one of these.
Wait, why isn't that going on forever?
Look at that.
It shoots two.
That's weird.
Interesting.
What if we do this?
I think I just like that.
But I don't like it on this one.
Was it the...
Oh, it adds 0.42 castellae.
Holy crap.
Holy damn.
Okay.
Oh, yeah, we need an ad mana.
We need ad manas for sure.
It does 11 damage.
I think I'm fine for now.
Dump, dump, dump.
I'll just do on this one.
Kind of shit.
And the recharge is bad.
But it's only for digging, right?
So if we do this...
I mean, that's already better.
But I don't know.
Maybe it's okay to have on this, even though it's a little slow.
It can dig.
That's all I need, right?
That's totally fine.
Totally fine.
All right, let's go.
So let me see here.
Purifying powder.
Hmm.
I have a feeling the purifying powder is gonna be important somewhere in the game.
Wait, so hold on.
Motherfucker.
Got him.
There we go.
All right.
Sweet!
We are back, baby.
Oh man, the chain bolt is something else.
So good.
Ow!
Holy crap!
Guys, calm the fuck down!
Was that guy, like, confused because he was on fire?
He didn't even attack me, did you notice?
Like, he was on fire and he just went like, Ah!
Ran around!
I feel like that's kind of a big deal.
If I put, like, enemies on fire, that is actually crowd control in a way.
Huh.
That's kind of big.
Whoa!
We're fine.
Oh my god, the screen is shaking so much.
It's hard to see what's going on.
The shake is real.
There we go.
Nice.
Awesome HP, but that's okay.
That's okay.
Oh, nice gold.
You.
Got him.
Yeah, nice.
I keep forgetting, I have teleport.
I have to remember this.
I also have digging, by the way.
Oh, it's so good!
I can't believe I've been sleeping on this spell for so long!
Look at this!
I don't care about this wall.
Let's go right through.
Oh yeah, I can just go like this.
Okay, it's kind of annoying to dig through gray rock when I have such a low rate of fire.
But, you know, it's what it is.
Get through here.
Nice.
And...
Oh, shit!
I didn't see that.
There's a bit of lava there.
Okay, that one is not good.
It is not.
There's something in there.
In fact, give me the gold, too.
Oh, okay.
Nice!
Dude, having...
Dude, I have an extra perk from now on.
That's actually insane.
Imagine if you get...
Okay, imagine getting the lottery and the extra perk.
Holy shit!
That is, like, potential for greatness.
I actually get this gold as well.
Oh no, I'm low on mana.
Ah, it's fine.
You know what?
Is there an option to...
Or, like, turn down the screen shake a bit?
There is!
Fantastic.
I may just put that at 10.
Because it actually does make me a little dizzy when the whole screen shakes like that.
For so long.
Um, that is...
Not really something I'm interested in.
No.
Oh my god, how do I get hit by that?
Unreal.
Oh, look at that.
Easy gold.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Wait, what?
Oh, there we go.
Oh, the lava was squirting on me.
I'm getting rich!
Okay, here's the plan for the cold pits.
I'm gonna get rich.
So that we can re-roll a million times if needed.
Oh, how did I not take damage?
That was kind of lucky.
Okay, we're fine.
Anything hiding here?
When is he such a...
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, oh, oh, be careful.
That was a bomb there.
I thought it was a chest at first.
But it wasn't.
Don't do it.
Nice.
Lovely.
That's lovely, that.
Oh, yeah.
My god, look at all that mess.
You know what I love about the chain bolt?
It fixes my shitty aim.
Oh, my goodness.
Holy enemy.
Oh, no, not one of those nests.
I don't actually have the means.
Or maybe I do.
I could use my energy orb.
Maybe.
Let's get up here.
Uh, water.
Okay, this is good, this is good.
I'm gonna keep shooting this guy.
Wait, am I even damaging it?
This is really difficult.
I think that works pretty well.
Okay, that works.
Nice.
I also feel like I'm stunning it when I hit it, so that it doesn't spawn any more of those flies.
Which is really nice.
Looks like a serious wand.
If you dig the fire, it actually disappears.
Mist of spirits.
A cloud of potent alcohol.
I'm trying to imagine why is this...
How is this good?
Let me think.
A cloud of potent...
Yeah, hold on, hold on, hold on.
So it makes you drunk.
So if I...
Okay.
If I put this on a trigger, and I shoot somebody, they're gonna get drunk, and their aim is gonna be fucked.
But sometimes that is not good for me when their aim is fucked, because sometimes you want the enemy to have predictable aim.
If they shoot randomly, and you start dodging, you like fly into it and shit.
Hold on, do I want this wand at all?
I mean, this wand is decent, but I will take this because of the heavy spread and...
Yeah, maybe I can do something with that.
Nice.
Oh, nice gold.
Give me gold.
Whoop!
That was a bit risky on my part.
Oh my god, look at all the gold!
Ah, so good.
I feel like the coal pit is a great place to farm some quick gold if you have good digging, you know?
Because of all the coal.
And it's super easy to dig through.
Oh, there's always this little...
elk cove here, with something in it.
Have you noticed?
That thing is repeating, man.
Is that blood potion?
Nah, I'm good, fam.
But what's down here?
I think I checked that wand.
Yeah, I did.
Let's go over here.
Nah, no one.
Get out!
Let's see what's over here.
A wand!
Yeah, right.
No thanks.
Yeah, I don't want it.
Wow!
Come to me.
That's how we do it in Kansas.
And nowhere else, only in Kansas.
We will always forget that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
What's down here?
I guarantee something's in there.
Watch.
Okay, never mind.
I do not guarantee it anymore.
I retract my statement.
I retract that bit about your cunt-fucking-kids.
That's such a good line.
One of my favorite movies in Bruges.
It's an inanimate fucking object.
That's the Okuskivi, man.
Oh, I'm scared of that.
Let's get rid of it.
That was violent.
A wand?
Yo!
A triple?
Would I like that?
I don't like that.
No, I don't want it.
I don't want it.
Nope.
Change my mind.
Shot through the wall.
Ah, hold on.
What is this?
Ah, it's nothing.
Oh, we have arrived.
We have arrived.
Should we get high?
Oh, man.
I kind of want to get high.
We could do it.
We could forget all our troubles.
And eat those shrooms.
Oh, an Okuskivi.
I just shot it off the...
Damn it.
Maybe that's a bad idea.
Turn every fucking thing.
Whoa!
Stay at range.
Do not engage in close quarters combat.
It's a bad idea.
There we go.
That worked pretty well.
Give me that gold.
Nah, that's too hard to dig.
Nope.
I think I should destroy these.
Otherwise, they're going to fuck me later.
I just know it.
Oh, it doesn't go that far.
If I find a big pile of fungus, I'm going to eat it.
Oh, look at that.
I pushed the Okuskivi down in the very unfortunate position.
I can't get near that.
I am terrified of that.
Imagine if I get teleported in there somehow by one of these fuckers in here.
You know what, I'm going to release the water.
Get the water out of there.
Also, I got to get into that wand anyway.
Shit, now it's down there.
I just made it worse.
Okay, solid.
I don't like how that looks, guys.
I do not like it.
Oh, oh shit, oh shit, oh shit, oh shit, oh shit, oh shit, oh shit, oh shit.
Wait, is that you doing that?
Stop it.
Oh, I'm seeing a lot of fungi.
I had a mini heart attack.
I can get it out of there.
Get it out of there.
It's too damn close to the metal.
Okay, I can work with that.
All right.
Useless.
I feel like I should pick it up.
Just keep it safe, you know, and put it somewhere responsibly.
Okay, oh no, oh no, it's one of those guys.
I'm kind of scared of those.
He has a wand as well.
Uh-oh, uh-oh, I did that not explode.
Hey, is he down there?
Nope, that's a gunner.
What the fuck is happening?
Oh, I think someone picked up the wand with the propane tanks and had a little bit of an accident.
That's what I think happened there.
Remember that wand?
Someone must have picked it up.
Where is this dude over here?
The dude who looks like me.
Dude, I wonder.
Hmm, I was about to say something dumb, nevermind.
I actually don't like those metal guys.
They make me unhappy.
That's honey.
You know what?
Oh shit.
I would like this berserkium.
I think that's going to come in handy down here.
I'm going to chug it all.
Oh, he's here, he's here.
Murder him.
I'm going to shoot through the walls.
Gotcha.
Gotcha, baby.
What kind of wand are we doing?
Ooh, an all-seeing eye.
You know what?
I'll take it.
That's pretty dope.
Uh-oh.
We got to shoot around the corners.
Okay.
Got him.
Nice.
Nice, nice, nice.
Dude, I'm going to drink all this.
Yo, I'm going to pick all this up and drink it.
What does that sound on here?
Oh, someone is being pheromoned.
I see.
Whoa.
I am going berserk.
What is all this stuff?
You know what?
I will take some pheromone.
We may need that in the next region.
That's a great idea, man.
Oh, yeah.
And now we can get high.
I'm going to do it.
Eat the mushrooms.
Oh, yeah.
I wonder what the limit is.
So when does this trigger?
Let's keep an eye.
Oh, wait.
I am oversatiated.
Shit.
I was eating vomit.
Okay, here we go.
Oh, no.
What happened?
Wait a minute.
Fuck.
Oh, no.
What does that mean?
That means something became lava, right?
That wasn't lava before?
Wait, how am I not still affected by berserk?
I had like a shit ton of berserkium.
Nice.
Now we remove the oil.
Yeah.
Okay.
I kind of want to explore more in this region, just because there's so many...
I have low HP.
Low HP.
Let's play it safe.
I'm already doing pretty well.
What's that?
I can't tell.
What kind of liquid that is?
Have I been up there?
I'm not sure.
I have.
Oh, okay.
So nobody did pick up that wand.
That was just a propane tank somewhere, then.
2,500 monies in the bank, guys.
I feel like I should leave.
But we still have 66 HP.
And maybe we find hearts.
What's over here?
Aha, look at that.
Thank the Lord above for thy gifts unto me.
I shall treasure it.
I kind of want to get high again.
I think I've already been here.
I have been here.
Yeah, I have been here.
Get this.
And then the gold spawned up here.
Interesting.
Maybe I'm overdoing it with the money here.
Nah, you can't overdo it.
There's no such thing as too little or too much money.
Nope.
Fucking get it while the getting is good, right?
Oh, that's a dense rock there.
Getting so rich.
What do we have here?
Oh, the energy orb is wildly good.
I'm so happy I discovered that.
Yoooo, good thing I stayed, huh, guys?
Holy crap.
Fuck the all-seeing eye.
Oh, kill that dude.
I feel like that was my cue to leave now.
I'm greedy.
I'm so greedy.
It's definitely a character flaw of mine.
It really is.
When it comes to games like this, I...
I'm so greedy.
Which is kind of ironic because when I play stuff like Dark Souls, I'm the complete opposite.
I'm the most patient gamer in the world.
Like, I will take a million years to go through a level and fucking bow everyone down.
Pulling enemies one by one.
Okay, I need to recharge some mana here.
Well, oh, whoop.
Not fast.
Not fast enough for me.
The fastest chain bolt in the West.
What's up, homies?
Check this out.
Called wall hack.
How did you not die?
All right, let's not blow that off.
Yeah, while we're down there, that would be a disastrous situation.
Okay, we've reached the end.
Okay.
Hold on.
Is this the same one I had with...
No.
There's a fire trail and there's a fiery trail.
I think.
This is different.
But still, I'm not entirely sure.
And I don't want to replace this one, obviously.
And neither do I want to replace my energy orb.
Because it's too good.
Okay, so I've been here, but is there something up here?
I kind of like being like a little worm, going through the terrain like this.
Because it also protects me from enemies most of the time.
I get to see what's there.
You know, in combination with my chain spell, I can hide in the terrain and just shoot them through the wall.
You know?
Pretty dope.
Oh my god!
Incredible!
I've noticed there's always something.
Or not always, but a lot of the time.
There's something in those pools of water.
In this level, specifically.
Okay, give me some here.
Look at all the money I possess.
I feel like I'm jinxing so hard.
I'm preparing myself mentally to lose everything.
It's okay, it's okay.
I should consider this run lost already.
That's the correct mental state to be in.
All right, we're leave.
Let's go.
Let's see what we got, huh?
Okay, nothing exciting.
Yo!
Whoa, what's that?
You're immune to electric damage, but metal and liquids around you electrify constantly.
Look out.
You're immune...
Dude.
Dude, that's actually insane.
Oh, but the problem is I can still get stunned, I guess.
And that's kind of dangerous.
But fire immunity.
Ooh, that's a good one.
I gotta take it, man.
I gotta take it.
No question, I gotta take that.
Any good ones?
So look at this one right here.
Oh, never mind.
Don't look at it.
Look away.
Okay, these all suck.
So here's what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna take all of my chainsaws and I'm gonna put them in my butt.
I don't know why I just said that.
Sorry, I'm in a silly mood, okay?
I apologize.
What can I do with this?
Maybe I can do something cool with a energy orb there.
That's not that cool.
That's not very cool at all.
I'm not intrigued.
Um...
Oh, but wait a minute.
This wand has an add mana on it!
The chainsaw is real, too.
The chainsaw is so real.
What if I do this?
That's not very exciting.
Why is that so slow?
Oh, because it adds a bunch of castellae, I guess.
What if I do this?
What does that mean?
Wait, what?
And it goes like brrr.
You see that?
Why is that not shown?
Or maybe it is and it's so fast, I miss it?
That's weird.
What if we had a...
Maybe all these chainsaws are messing things up.
Wait a minute.
Chainsaws are kind of sick.
So many of them.
I've never had this many chainsaws before.
What the hell?
Let's say I do something like that.
Hello?
What just happened?
Yo, that's nuts.
Hello?
This add mana is not enough.
It's too crazy.
Oh!
Guys.
Damn!
Holy shit!
That is a lot of damage right there.
Whoa.
What if I keep going?
Oh my...
Wait, what?
Is that actually doing anything?
I think that made it worse.
Hold on, I can test the DPS.
Let's test the DPS.
Test the DPS.
Ooh, that's not bad.
That's really good.
But hold on.
Jesus.
Wait.
Oh, I have infinite mana!
Wait, wait, wait.
Why, why, why, why do I have that?
Huh?
Wait, okay, hold on.
So it casts mana always.
So it starts by casting that.
That's an...
Dude, it's because it casts it on everyone.
No way!
Did that make it worse?
Hold on.
Yeah, it totally...
There's a sweet spot here.
Oh my lord!
Okay, then I run out of mana, but like this?
Infinite.
I'm not gonna try and understand why that is, guys.
I'm just gonna accept what's happening, what I'm seeing with my eyes.
I don't get it, but this is fun.
This is great.
This is really nice.
That's gonna do a ton of damage.
And it's like seeking enemies too.
That's gonna be insanity style.
Um, yeah, man.
Grab these.
Okay.
Then I can do stuff like...
No?
Whoops.
No!
Yeah!
Nah, run out of mana.
Run out of mana like that.
What if I do this?
Hold on.
Is that even more crazy?
Hold on a second.
390, it seems.
If I remove this?
300!
That is more!
Hold on.
Let's test the sweet spots.
Okay, that's worse.
Let's remove one more.
390?
Oh, then I run out of mana.
Okay.
Now I don't.
390.
That's interesting, isn't it?
It's very weird.
But I love it.
That is sick.
Imagine having a extra damage on that as well.
Oh, baby.
I definitely need this, I think.
We gotta have a digger of some sort.
Well, we can't make that any faster, right?
Not like that, at least.
Maybe up here?
So, what's happening is, it's removing recharge, right?
But it's...
Oh, the castile is kind of low, I guess.
Oh, but it adds a lot of castile here.
Let me fill it up with this, see how that works.
Yeah, I'm not quite sure.
The chainsaw is the biggest mystery of this game.
I shit you not.
It is insanity.
And you know what else?
I'm going to put light on this.
Put it...
Look at that, it's beautiful and bright, just like fireworks.
And now I can see things too.
That is fantastic.
That's even better than before now.
Dude, burning trail, we're a mode to fire!
Oh, but hold on.
No, definitely.
Yeah, yeah, we're going to do that.
We're going to do that.
Okay.
Um, and I think I'm actually done.
I do have a lot of money, so I should maybe buy some of these.
Oh, hold on, hold on.
So, burning trail, a tail of fire, gives the projectile a trail of fiery particles.
Let's do both.
Dude, I just had an idea.
Why don't I add this as well?
Is this too crazy?
Maybe it is.
Maybe...
Okay.
No, definitely.
We're going to leave it like this.
I'm going to leave it like that.
And we're going to add the fire trail as well.
Because fuck it, why not?
Oh, that's interesting.
Look at that, the way it drops off like that.
But I guess there's a bigger chance of that destroying explosives in its path.
But dude, the projectiles themselves are going to do that just fine on their own, you know?
So I think this is okay.
We could add a, oh my god, fireball orbit?
I'm going to be immune to that, no?
Hold on.
Am I going to be immune to that?
Oh, we're going to make this insane.
I block it, guys!
I'm immune!
Oh, but I run out of mana.
Okay, okay, hold on, hold on.
Maybe if I massage it a little bit, maybe somehow it...
Oh, that's interesting.
Maybe if I add it inside of here?
Not quite.
What if I do that?
Okay, not quite either.
Okay, I think that's too much mana.
We may be pushing this a little too hard.
Oh, also, I did something just now.
I don't have infinite mana anymore.
I did something.
What did I do?
No.
What did I change?
There we go.
Wait a minute.
Now we only do 300.
390, there it is.
That's the damage I was looking for.
What if we put this in here?
What the fuck?
Ah, we run out of mana.
That is crazy, though.
Oh, hold on.
I fucked it up again.
There it is.
Is this still 390?
What did I...
Oh, there it...
Oh, wait a minute.
We're...
Okay, we don't have infinite mana then.
What did I have before that made this work?
Oh, you know what?
It's probably this extra mana being drained using these.
Yeah, I think I want this instead.
Let's do that.
That's better.
That extra damage is gonna come in, I'm pretty sure, and be helpful.
Okay, is there anything else we could maybe add?
I think that's it.
I think we're good, fam.
Let's put some of this up here.
Firebolt.
Put it on the floor.
Do I want to carry around all these chainsaws?
Actually, I could just make a chainsaw want.
Why not?
Why shouldn't I make a chainsaw want?
Eh?
Not bad.
I think I like it.
In fact, is it maybe even better up here?
That's sort of the same, I guess.
I think I like it.
Let me put this stuff up here.
And we are good to go, man.
Oh, dude, this is fun.
Let's go.
Let's go check out this wand, huh?
Isn't that exciting?
Maybe I'll leave this wand here.
Kind of useless right now.
Unless...
Hold on, should I put something in there?
Probably this one.
I still want to be able to do that, I think.
What if I do this?
Whoops.
I really want to make this fast.
Why don't these make it fast?
Okay, yeah.
Well, you know what?
The thing about the chainsaw for me is just try a bunch of shit and see if it works.
That's like the way I do it, you know?
Okay, that's fine.
Let's move!
All right.
Sup, fools?
That is an interesting wand I've got here.
I gotta say, that is some crazy shit.
Is that a worm?
Are we worming?
Uh-oh.
Holy shit.
That guy died.
Okay.
Let me see what's on that wand.
Whoop.
The only weakness of this wand is that it has very low range.
Levitation.
Concentrated light.
Reduces castile.
Hmm.
Hold on a second here.
I'm having way too much fun with this wand I have here, guys.
This is just...
completely insane.
Kind of want to try it with the light.
The only issue I have with this wand is that when you shoot it, you literally cannot see anything else on the screen.
So it's hard to dodge projectiles.
But I guess that's true of anyone that goes a little nuts, right?
A broken wand!
Nice!
And there is a small delay before this one actually shoots when you press the button.
Because there is an inherent delay on the chain bolt.
Uh, I want this for sure.
So I'm gonna get rid of...
Ah, that's kind of...
Maybe get rid of this one.
I don't need the tablet anymore.
Fuck that shit.
Yeah, fuck it.
Get that.
Okay.
Oh, let's use a lot of water?
That's actually kind of useful.
Dude!
Goodbye, Toxic!
Why wouldn't I just put that on my main wand?
Fire and...
Fire and water is gonna be the elemental wand.
I kind of want to put a long distance cast if I find it on this one too.
But I do kind of need it for my teleport.
Dude, this one is fun!
Why is that not blowing up?
That is worrying me.
How come that's not blowing up?
Wait, my wand is also digging pretty well.
Sort of.
Not really.
Kind of.
I guess the chainsaw can do it in a pinch.
Okay, there.
Dude, this wand right here is gonna be insane in the Heezy Base.
I can shoot through walls with this.
Oh!
So many snipers!
In fact, the game audio is trouble keeping up with this wand here.
Honestly, I am surprised how well this game runs.
Like, it does crash a few times, but...
Depending... like, just given the amount of shit that happens in the game, and that needs to be calculated at all times...
I'm impressed.
I really am.
It's... the game's a champ.
Whoa!
Nope.
Oh, wow.
That is a big...
Whoa!
It dropped the heart?
The hell?
I've never seen that?
That's... that's awesome!
Lovely.
Okay.
Load that up.
What a fireworks display this is.
Maybe there's a bit too much going on with this wand.
You know, it can get...
maybe to be a little too much at times.
Or maybe not.
I don't know.
Is that gonna explode?
Okay.
By the way, we ate fungus.
I still don't know exactly what happened with that.
I haven't noticed anything out of the ordinary yet.
Pea soup?
Wait!
Speaking of...
Oh!
Wait, what?
Did lava become...
Pea soup?
That's fucking crazy!
Can I eat it?
Is it delicious?
Hold on.
I need to find a place to...
Oh, I can...
Hold on.
You're feeling pressure inside.
Cause ingesting...
Pea soup?
Wait, you mean like...
I need to fart?
Is that what's happening here?
I am so confused.
So confused.
Oh wow!
I didn't even see you.
Holy shit, dude!
This guy is Jason Bourne!
Fuck off, will ya?
Where's the other guy?
Okay.
Why does this look like Heezy Base?
Doesn't it kind of look like Heezy Base?
That is very weird.
Dude, fucking lava became Pea soup.
That is so...
Insane.
I love it.
I don't mind that at all.
I prefer Pea soup over lava any day of the week.
Did you see how that is digging at various intervals?
I think that's because of the fire modifier I have that is actually melting the snow.
Yeah, pretty dope.
Also, we're low on HP here.
Just getting to be a little...
dangerous.
Just a bit.
There's a gun there.
Whoop.
Where's all that?
What's happening here?
Oh!
Oh, we have light!
Look!
That's why I put light on it!
Isn't that amazing?
Uh, I'm not getting up there.
But I can actually teleport through.
Boy, flimoxium.
Whoa, sniper!
Oh,
this motherfucker hit me still.
The snipers are the bane of my existence because I have such little range.
What the hell is this kind of path?
That's scary.
That could have gone really bad.
That I had a closing counter with death just there.
I'm telling you.
Oh, this reduces water.
That's right.
Let me in!
No, I don't think I will.
I think we're leaving.
It's time.
No, hold on.
Should I explore that?
Wait a minute.
I mean, I'm tempted, man.
No, we can always come back.
We can always come back.
That's a bit too scary for me.
Let's go.
All right, man.
Not bad at all.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, healing bolt.
I like that.
And then we have...
What's that?
Revenge explosion?
Healthy exploration.
Chance to duplicate.
No, no, I'm gonna, I'm gonna do that.
No more shock.
Oh,
dude.
Depending on the wand you have, that could, that could make it really cool.
But I already have a good wand.
Stainless armor.
This one could be neat.
I'm tempted to reroll again.
But we are kind of early in the run, so...
And this is kind of a good perk.
So I may take it.
Yeah, let's just take it.
That's good.
It's a good perk.
Let's not overthink things.
Now this thing here, doubles, no, reduced spread.
That could come in really handy on this one.
Couldn't it?
Let's see it now.
Yo, that really does reduce the spread.
Let's try with this.
That looks cool, man.
Let's see.
Doesn't do as much damage, though.
Yep.
What about the old spark?
Oh, that's terrible.
Absolutely terrible.
What if we were to just replace...
Oops, do that.
What happens then?
Okay.
Okay, dude.
Honestly, this is not bad.
But then again.
Where is it?
That one is not bad either, right?
This is actually pretty dope.
Especially now that it's such a tight line.
Like, that is cool.
And it also gives me more visibility.
Piercing shot.
What is that again?
Makes a projectile fly through enemies, but harmful to the caster.
Fly through enemies.
Harmful to...
How is that...
That seems like...
I would love for this to be harmful to the enemies and fly through the caster.
Like, I want the opposite of this.
Reduces damage by 15 as well.
Hold on.
Why is this good?
Why would I use this?
It cost 140 mana?
This has to...
I'm missing something.
I'm missing something here.
Makes a projectile fly through...
Actually, okay.
I know why it's good.
It's because most projectiles get stopped when they hit an enemy.
This will make it go, of course, through everyone.
And you can hit...
It's like great AOE, basically.
You can do some crazy AOE with this.
And if I have, like, another add mana, I can maybe even put this in here and make it super nice.
But projectiles will hurt me.
So that's kind of a shitty situation.
What's this?
A large fireball.
I want this, of course.
Imagine a bolt with rejuvenated power.
So, okay.
The way I did that last time is I had it on...
Well, I don't have that here, but I had, like, a boomerang type effect where it would come back on me.
But actually, I have an idea.
What if we do this from down here?
Wait, what happened?
Also, this is actually not that much healing if you think about it.
Damage healing is minus nine.
So, you heal...
And I only have 19 of these.
And I don't think this one...
What do you call it?
Even if I find unlimited spells, this is not gonna work on that.
Hmm.
I guess I'll have to think about it.
Okay.
I think I want to put water trail on this one up here, guys.
Oh, that's gonna produce way too much water, I think.
And that can be really dangerous if there's electricity, because I'm gonna be swimming in water at all times, and that's really bad.
Yeah, let's not do that.
That's a bad idea.
Bad idea.
Let's not even fucking entertain that thought for a moment.
I do want something that digs.
Something solid.
Luminous drill is solid, but...
We need to spam it, basically.
And I'm not sure we can do that comfortably here.
Although, hold on, we have this.
That is not with a timer.
This costs 10 mana, this costs 30.
There's a huge difference.
Okay, so now I do this.
Now we're fucking talking.
Yes!
Very good, very good, very good.
And maybe we can even...
Oh, I want this so bad.
Fireball orbit.
What if I... hold on a second.
I have an idea, I have an idea.
Wait, what?
Oh, I think the lifetime is not enough.
This one, yeah.
Oh, that's rip.
It's kind of annoying.
I mean, that's pretty, that's pretty sick.
I want to see if I can't put it up here somehow.
It's just so insane, isn't it?
We need another ad mana for that, unfortunately.
What?
I think I like what I saw here.
I mean, we run out of mana fast, but it'll be enough to dig a little bit.
It's not bad.
Now this one, healing bolt.
Let me actually shoot it one more time.
I know it's kind of a...
We can always get spell refresh, I guess.
Let me see.
Wait.
I thought this...
Wait, what?
Oh, wait a minute.
I just healed myself.
I thought that for some reason the lifetime of this was so low, but what actually happened is I absorbed it before.
Okay, nevermind.
We're good to go.
That's our heal.
We did it, boys.
Easy as that.
Easy as pie.
In fact, I think pies are pretty hard, actually.
I take it back.
Easy as...
Something else.
Not pie.
And then I want...
I think I want all my chainsaws here, just because I like having a chainsaw.
I like the chainsaw.
What can I say?
I like sawing chains.
Or should I do this?
Oh, but hold on.
Put this here instead.
Then we can...
Why is that so...
Why is it going that fast now?
Oh, it's because I'm using the wrong grill.
Fuck, you scared me, Dan.
You scared the crap out of me.
Invading my home like that.
My goodness.
Sir, all right now.
Okay, I think we're ready.
Let's fucking go.
Hold on.
Is there anything else I needed to buy?
Actually, energy orb.
30 mana drain.
The last one I had was...
Much more expensive, right?
Oh my god.
I'm a...
Fuck yeah, I'm so glad.
I just went back.
Dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude.
Maybe this is actually sick here now.
Oh, it's not.
Never mind.
I mean, it's dope, but it's not that dope, you know?
Hold on.
0.17, 0.52.
Let me just quickly see here.
Why is that so slow?
What is the difference?
0.17, 0.55.
There's almost no...
What?
Add more.
Wait, I don't get it.
I don't get it.
This...
Huh?
Wait, that's very odd.
Look at this.
Oh, wait a minute.
It's because it's casting two spells per cast.
I think that's it.
That's the difference.
So one, two, one, two.
If I do this...
It's good for digging.
That's a good digger right there.
Lovely.
Now we go.
Oh, yeah, baby.
All right.
Easy base.
Let's freaking go.
Blow everything up.
Rid of all the lamps.
All potential electricity.
Get it out of here.
Look at this.
Through the wall.
It's so good in here.
Oh.
Also, I felt the audio bugging a little bit there.
I'm scared of crashes.
Oh, this is perfect for this area.
You know what?
I'm going to restart the game.
I'm too scared.
Restart.
Maybe I should make a backup of my folder.
Hold on.
I'm actually that scared.
This is actually a good run.
I don't want this shit to crash.
What's it called?
Nala Games.
I'm just going to copy the whole folder just to be safe.
Put it there.
All right.
It's copying.
Done.
Open Steam.
Noita.
All right.
Cheers, everybody.
Had to take a sip.
Gotta stay hydrated.
Whoa!
Don't go in there.
Bad idea.
This weapon right here is a little bit...
What do you call it?
Unpredictable when it comes to...
Or it's not very reliable when it comes to destroying explosives like that.
That's the kind of scary.
Mix up the water, please.
Oh, am I freezing shit?
What?
Huh?
Why are things freezing?
I guess because it's cold.
Wow.
Okay.
That did a lot of damage.
You.
Through the wall.
Oh, yeah, I'm immune to fire.
Forgot about that.
Ah, shit.
Oh, shit, get out of the way.
The audio is already bugging again.
I feel like the game is not liking the wand I've made.
Shit.
Bro, this one is actually nuts.
It just spread to every enemy instantaneously.
And you know what?
This one I have there is actually not the worst either.
Like when it comes to just straight up killing.
Levitation.
Look at this, a drill.
We could activate it if we want to.
It needs electricity and it needs some oil.
Whoa.
That was scary.
Very scary.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, no, no.
That was a friendo.
Ah, rip.
He was dead.
Shit.
Friendos are bros.
The way it splits off at the end is nuts.
I do wonder if the fire that I produce can somehow reduce the freezing vapor.
But it doesn't seem like that's the case.
Dude, I imagine this one would be pretty good against the bosses that have a shield too.
Because it goes through walls, could go through a shield.
Right?
That excites me a little bit.
Whoa.
Scary.
Oh, shit, there's a fucking thing right there.
Get rid of it.
My fire reducing the...
It's not.
It just dissipates over time.
There's got to be a way to somehow eliminate it, right?
Whoa.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
There's electricity there.
Scary.
Oh, stay here in the flames.
Stay nice and hot.
Oh, toasty, toasty.
You're on fire.
Find some...
No, I don't want to find water.
I want to stay on fire.
Because I am on fire right now.
Get it?
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
Dude, it's time.
It is time.
What do we got?
Some triplicate bolts.
That could be pretty dope on this one.
With another reduced spread.
Let's keep this one in mind.
I'm going to find some water and try and heal myself.
We're at half HP.
I guess we can do that at the mountain, right?
That's like confirmed.
Yeah, let's head up.
Back to the mountain.
This fucker hit me?
Nah, I don't think he did, actually.
Don't even do it.
I wonder if you can find straight up electricity resistance, like, and not just with the...
but everything is being electrified.
Just straight up electricity immunity.
I haven't seen that yet.
If I see it, I'm going to take it.
No questions asked.
That goes straight into my veins.
It's actually one of the few things I'm super scared of, like, right now.
Okay, um, wait, what was I doing?
Oh yeah, healing.
Let's see, let's see, let's see.
Doesn't heal a lot here, but let's see, 122.
Shit.
It doesn't work.
Wait, am I hitting the fish?
No fucking way.
What?
Wait, what?
Oh, there we go, there we go!
Yes!
It's happening!
Holy shit, I was donating to the fish!
That's incredible.
Oh yeah, we can even spam it a little bit.
Oh, nice.
Oh, that's so good, that's so good!
Lovely stuff.
Oh, we're out, so now we do this.
Hehe!
That is guaranteed, I mean, it's not a lot of healing, but it's something.
So imagine if I had like 20 of these.
I had that once, remember?
That was a one we found that just had a shit ton of these on it.
And then you find the spell refresher and you just have all those back.
Actually broken.
Okay, cool.
I am...
Wait a minute.
No, that's fine.
Let's go.
I was about to say, let's try to triplicate both, but I didn't bring that.
All right, let's keep exploring.
I need to find more hearts.
I can light up the other side, it's so good.
Whoa, hello.
Wow, treasure chest does not get destroyed by the chain bolt.
There was a bomb in there, I think.
Instantly exploded too.
You know what's nice about the energy orb?
When you shoot like stuff like these lamps that will also electrify these surroundings, it actually digs through it and removes it from the game.
So it doesn't even have a chance to electrify shit.
It's important.
Oh, that was a big bang.
This digging is nuts.
It's so good.
Sniper in the building.
It's a homie.
Oh dude, and now I know what I... I need to soil my pants.
Wait a minute.
Don't you heal him?
Don't you fucking heal him?
I need to get the soil spell, then I can trap this guy somewhere.
If I have the soil spell, that's the strategy.
Hold on, I gotta take care of this guy.
And his friend.
Follow me, man.
Come here.
Oh yeah.
Oh, it's so good.
Can I somehow trap him?
I'm gonna bring him...
I'm gonna try once more to bring him back to the holy mountain.
Last time I tried this, he somehow left.
He betrayed me.
I had an idea with some black holes and some long-distance cast stuff, but I don't have that right now, so...
Come here.
Come here, you.
That's it, come on.
There we go.
Yeah, come on, come on.
No, no, no.
Come on.
Yes, there we go, buddy.
This is Trevor.
Everyone say hi to Trevor.
Trevor, come here.
Follow me up here and just go through the wall.
Come on, Trevor, through the wall.
You can do it.
Yes, come on.
There we go.
That's a good boy.
Come here.
That's right.
He's probably just gonna wander on out of here.
Do I have a way of actually trapping him?
Let me think.
If I can put him in a bath of pherom...
No, wait a minute.
That doesn't work.
I'm just gonna do what I did last time.
Bring it over here and just run.
Who knows?
Maybe he stays this time.
Maybe I get lucky.
All right, see ya.
See ya, Trevor.
Have fun.
I'm even gonna go this way first, so that if he follows me directly, he's gonna go sort of down and can't follow me.
Do you know what I mean there?
I think it makes sense.
Yo, what's happening there?
Oh, wait.
Fully cooked meat.
Oh, delicious.
No, a friendo.
Oh, whatever.
I was a bit too fast on the trigger there.
Too bad.
What's over here?
Okay, long distance enemies or my enemy?
What's that?
Unstable polymorphine.
I don't think I enjoy that.
That is a no enjoyment.
No enjoyment.
Dense steel.
What's up, fools?
Wow, it went through there, and then it went through there as well.
Wait, what?
How are you not polymorphed?
That's insane.
That's some water.
We have a chest.
Money!
Ooh, careful.
What's happening?
Why are we electrifying things?
Freezing gaze!
Now I just need unlimited spells.
And then we're home free.
That is good stuff.
Dude, freezing gaze with reduced scatter or reduced spread?
Oh, we've had a dope.
Oh, there's a heart!
I have to teleport in there.
I think that's a bad idea, guys.
It's the only way.
I can't get through steel.
Unless I can turn that into water somehow from here.
Let me think.
That's a definite...
I don't think I'm going to do a situation.
Unless I find a plasma cutter or something.
Just had nothing there.
Stuck in the wall.
I heard a sniper.
Oh, that's brutal what I'm doing here.
Oh, that's so brutal.
Through the wall, bitches.
The ultimate safe encounter.
We get all the monies.
In the seep.
I'll take it.
I shall acquire that.
Oh, he has a wand!
But I think it's a wand I recognize.
It's the freezing gaze.
Yep.
Everything gets blown up.
He has a wand too!
You know, that is actually a lot of damage.
Large spitter bolt.
With timer though.
I don't think I enjoy timers.
Timers make me itchy.
You know?
It's a wand.
Whoa, hello.
Yo!
Oh, all the gold down here.
Below the thrill.
I guess there's always that.
Nice.
That's a lot of money.
Oh wait, freezing vapor, freezing vapor.
Be careful.
Come on.
I think I'm playing pretty well here.
Just wait for that to go away.
It's time to heal again, I think.
You know what?
I'm going back.
It's time to heal.
Actually, wait a minute.
What's up with all that blood in there?
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Can I?
Oh, it's close.
Damn it.
I gotta get rid of that sand or whatever that is.
Okay.
We're back in the base.
Let's see if my friend is here.
Hey, Trevor!
Oh my god, this is sick, guys.
Look at this.
That's so cool.
Oh yeah.
That's, that's easy healing there.
Fuck yeah, man.
Come here.
All right, let's go.
Didn't even need to use my healing bolt.
I feel like I have advanced strategies running right now.
Fucking trapping a...
Heezy guy in there that I come back to.
He's like my prisoner, you know?
He's healing me and shit.
It's so cool.
Oh, look, a chest.
I don't trust it going...
Because if that's an Ukuskivi, right?
Yeah, exactly.
We got to do it like that.
Because there's metal surfaces, and that's how I fucked up one run last time, remember?
I have learned from my mistakes.
What the fuck is that?
That's always scary when those things explode.
That was a little bit risky what I did there.
Oh, that was a bomb hidden in the snow.
I love easy base, man.
Favorite area.
I'm getting rid of all these potential dangers.
Imagine if I could turn off the master switch somewhere and turn off all electricity in this place, so all the lamps are off.
Oh my god, is that a broken wand?
No fucking way.
Yes, please.
I'll leave this here.
Awesome.
Let's go back and see what's in it.
Also, I'm going to explore a little bit while I'm going.
Wait, where am I now?
Oh, release the assets!
Or toxic sludge, I guess.
Yeah, let's not jump through the wall there.
It's a bit risky.
Go like a normal person.
Or circular.
In fact, give me some of that.
Yeah, why not?
There we go.
Green glimmer and a bunch of fire bolts.
I don't like the shovel though.
That makes me sad.
Yeah, I don't want it.
It's worth trying though.
Holy shit, that caught me off guard.
That was a fucking thing embedded in the snow.
Uh-oh.
Huh.
Trifort.
Crashed in three spells and a trifurcated pattern.
Nah.
Actually, the wand is not too bad.
I've seen worse.
I guess he got the wand from here.
Chest.
Anything in there?
Okay.
I'm gonna destroy it and instantly teleport out.
What?
No fucking way.
What is all this?
Facing arc?
Uh, get rid of water, I guess.
What the fuck?
This contained a lot of shit.
Long distance cast.
My beloved.
Get rid of this one.
Iplicate spell?
Weakening curse projectiles?
No way.
Hold on.
Target hit by a projectile takes 25% extra projectile damage for a time?
That's crazy.
That is a straight up damage buff.
Holy crap.
Makes the projectile fly much slower, but teleports short distances so it's fly right, right, right, right, right.
All right, cool.
Very unexpected for a chest to contain multiple spells like that.
Friendo!
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, we gotta be careful here.
We gotta do this tactfully.
Oh, no, friendo.
You don't wanna come this way.
Wait, are they shooting each other now?
What the fuck are you guys doing?
Don't you kill friendo.
All right, I made it.
That was incredible.
Heal me.
Get in the pheromone.
A little to the right.
A little to the...
Sir.
That's it, friend.
Heal me up.
This is insane.
This pheromone trick is actually wild.
Oh, no.
No!
Rip.
F's in the chat.
Oh, I see that.
A little fucking trap lurking.
Ambrosia.
Not bad.
I will acquire.
Oh, wait, that's polymorphine.
Why did the thing not explode?
Odd.
Oh, that was a bit scary there.
There's also a heart and some toxic shit somewhere.
I just don't trust going in there, man.
I need to find something like a laser cutter.
And receive it, that's mine.
I left that there.
Boom.
Oh.
That's cool, I guess.
You know what?
I'll drink it.
Oh, wait, that's toxic sludge on the bottom.
Let's fix that.
Oh, yeah, look at that.
Now mix.
Mix, I said.
Yes.
Now I drink.
Slurp, slurp, slurp.
How is the digging now?
Dude, berserkium is actually something I need to experiment with more.
Because it actually amplifies spells in a way that is not described by the potion.
Like, look at that, the radius is bigger.
That's not obvious that that happens.
So now I wonder what else could happen with different spells.
Wait, what?
Oh!
What is this one again?
Oh, I have so much money anyway.
Also, is there something above me again?
Oh, there is, look!
Holy shit.
Okay.
Hold on.
What is this?
Cast a copy of a projectile behind you.
But the copies still cost mana.
The copy of a projectile.
Behind you.
It's a utility item.
Okay.
I gotta experiment with that.
What's this?
Oh, light shot.
That's the thing that's really good with black holes.
Um...
I don't think I want this.
Or that.
Or this.
Accelerative homing.
You know, I think that is really good with a rock.
Like, really good.
We just need to find unlimited spells first.
That one is nice.
Okay, hold on.
Can we even get up here?
Oh, wait, wait.
Yes, we can.
Yes.
Actually.
Look at the eye.
What if we fill this with teleportation?
Just like the portals.
They have this underneath them.
I mean, I don't have any right now, but...
Also, I just noticed it looked like giant hands on the sides.
Look at that.
Why is that...
Why is this sort of going inward as if it's a gravitational pull of some sort?
Hmm.
I don't know.
I mean, I can fill it with blood, at least.
But do I have any polymorphine?
Or, like, teleportation anywhere?
I don't think I do.
Hmm.
You there.
Come here.
God, I love the fucking long distance teleport.
It is...
It changes the entire game.
Oh, hello.
Hey, come here.
Thank you.
Oh, what do we have here?
Yeah, no.
No, thanks.
I don't want to kill myself.
Because I will kill myself.
I'm actually so happy I put light on this.
It actually makes a huge difference.
I think I should start doing that from now on with all of my primary ones.
It's just so good.
Also, am I...
I have 12% pheromone left.
I don't even know if that's enough to seduce one of these guys.
Gotta find some more.
Dude, I feel like Heezy Base is way bigger of an area than, say...
the hemisphere.
Like, it's actually bigger.
Oh, here we go, here we go.
All right, sir.
Come here.
Come to me.
If I can make...
Oh, hello, what's that?
Oh, hello.
Oh, no.
No!
Oh, you're gonna die, bitch.
You bastard.
Wow.
That's unreal.
Dammit, man.
Everyone dies now.
I'm gonna find some blood.
I want money.
Uh, do I wanna...
Yeah, go.
Get rid of that one.
Holy morphine.
And there's another portal.
Anything in there?
Look at that, we can just spy with our eye.
I mean, with our wand.
Wait, that was a bit sketchy.
Let the water flow.
That was close.
I can't believe this happened, by the way.
That makes me really wanna...
find more chests.
Like, look how big this area is.
I feel like I keep wandering around and finding new spots, even though I feel like I've already been here, sort of.
But then, not really.
It just keeps going.
Oh, a bunch of persecium.
Consume it.
We're eating off the ground.
Oh yeah, oh yeah.
Eat it all.
Actually, we have blood here.
I'm gonna grab it.
And I guess I could just, uh, saw some corpses, if I needed to.
That's a way to get blood.
Wait!
Are there two drills?
Didn't I already dig below one of these?
Whoa!
What?
What the fuck?
I'm so confused.
I thought I already dug below one of them.
I just messed with my mind.
Oh.
Oh, there's money.
We need more blood.
More blood, baby.
Dum, dum, dum, dum, dum, dum, dum.
Oh, what's that?
Oh, it's molten steel.
Thought it was gold.
Okay, we're back here now.
I see.
Uh, I need to find a bit more blood.
That's really what I need.
There we go.
Blood me up, baby.
Also...
Yeah, that's fine.
Yeah, that's a bit more.
So, there's all kinds of other stuff in there.
Oh, be careful.
Oh, did you see my preemptive hovering in the air there?
Precautionary hovering.
Smart play.
All right, we may have enough blood now.
Would like to find just a...
There we go.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, hello there.
Goodbye.
Oh, man.
Should I?
No, I'm half HP.
I'm not gonna risk it.
Fuck that.
Unless...
I...
There is actually a way I can get this, guys.
I go back.
Long distance cast water.
Turn into water.
Teleport in.
Get it out.
I'm gonna do that after.
That's the plan.
That's actually insane.
Okay, here we go.
All right.
Let's fill it.
Okay, I also filled it with all kinds of other things.
Hopefully, that's all right.
We'll have to see.
What's happening?
Hold on.
Oh, no.
Oh!
Oh,
shit!
Oh, shit!
Shit!
Well!
Well, well, well.
Okay.
That...
That was scary, man.
Jesus.
All right.
Well, end of that run.
One of the best runs I've had in a while.
Just over like that.
That is fucking brutal.
I'm not gonna lie, guys.
I have a big scar on my heart right now.
All right.
Apparently, the impact of the teleport spell is enough to break glass.
That's good to know, I guess.
Good knowledge to have.
Ah, I really did not think that was possible.
But now we know if we break the glass.
It's bad news.
Don't do it.
Don't break the glass.
I saw my death coming as well as soon as everything started collapsing.
I was panicking, man.
What I should have done was immediately teleport out of there.
I just didn't think quick enough.
It is what it is.
Shit!
That's really unfortunate.
But that was a good run.
That was a solid run.
There we go.
I got it.
In fact, I'm even gonna grab the tablet.
Just because I'm here.
Is it gonna roll downhill?
Oh, wait a minute.
It's gonna be a little hard to get.
Nah, fuck it.
I'm grabbing the other tablet.
Wow, it is so...
Has it ever been this dark?
Look at this.
It's midnight.
Very atmospheric.
Okay, that's fun.
That was actually really fun.
Oh, hold on.
I have spark bolts.
Okay, gotcha.
All right, let's move.
Do do do do.
Oh,
go this way.
A chest already.
Oh my god, what a start, guys.
That's really nice.
I could...
Be careful with that.
Holy crap.
That will set myself on fire.
Gotta remember that.
But I was like, I can just grab some gold like that too.
Like, it's not the most efficient digger, but if the gold is right at the surface there, I may as well take it.
Low shit up.
Set shit on fire.
Cause mayhem.
Ooh, here we go, here we go.
Massive firework.
And now I should be careful.
Yeah, that's not good.
That's not good.
We got a retreat.
This is where a tablet would be really handy.
I'm going to go...
Ah, actually.
All this water here makes me think maybe there's something in the water.
Yeah, I can't see.
Oh, shit.
Whoop.
Nice.
Love me a trigger.
Love me a digger.
Hurry, he's coming.
Oh.
Oh, my heart.
That was scary, dude.
What is this stuff?
Oh, I'm abusing.
I don't give a shit.
Clean the surfaces.
There we go.
What do we got?
Horizontal path.
Picking bolts.
Energy your baby.
Oh, I don't even have the money.
What's that?
Circle of fire.
I will be back for you.
Just need a bit of that green.
Just a bit.
Energy orb has become one of my favorite spells now.
It's so good.
It is fantastic.
Acceleration.
That guy's gonna die.
I'm gonna let him die.
Have fun down there.
Now I take a dip.
Give me that gold.
Mix it.
Worm fer...
Take it.
Nothing like some worm pheromone.
Oof.
Kivaskivi.
Look at all the hortas.
It's a whole family up there.
Hey, guys.
Oh, no.
Oh, wait.
Explosive.
That was scary.
Okay, okay.
Yeah.
Let's wait a bit.
Oh, no.
It's frogs.
Oh, I didn't even see you there.
Oh, I think we're bagging ourselves into a corner here.
It's not looking good.
Dude, that thing does a shit ton of damage.
Are you shitting me?
He did like 20 damage to me.
Oh, one.
Yeah, you know what?
I'm leaving.
Ookuskivi.
All that?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
No.
No, thank you.
I reject.
I do not let Ookuskivi into my heart.
Oh, my God.
I'm almost dead.
We got to leave.
So they have a blind spot right above them, if you notice.
No, wait.
He's burning.
He's confused.
Fuck, fuck.
Okay, we're leaving.
Run.
That got a little too close there at the end.
Just a bit too close.
Guys, long distance.
Oh, but there's no teleport.
But that's okay.
I'm happy with what I'm seeing.
What do we got here?
Critical hit plus.
You know what?
Did I ever try that?
I'm not sure it did.
I may just try it.
What is this one?
Square barrier.
That one I want.
And what's this?
Electric torch.
That is just not good.
Unless you put it on a trigger.
Also, I forgot to buy the spells in the last level.
But that's okay.
I mean, we were about to die anyway, so.
It is what it is.
Now, the digging bolts.
Dude, this is this combo right here.
That is actually a sick combo because the damage from the drill is eight.
Wait, why is that not?
Oh, I guess maybe the damage from this doesn't show up.
Because it's kind of weird, isn't it?
Oh, man, I have shuffle ones up the wazoo.
It's the...
Oh, that sucks.
Let me think.
Maybe it's okay.
Maybe shuffle is all right if I do this.
Maybe it doesn't matter which...
No, it sucks.
It definitely sucks.
What if I do that?
Nah, hold on.
No, I definitely like this, I think.
Although, damage slice is even more, right?
Thirteen damage.
Yo, that's even better.
Yo, that's sick!
Hello?
This simple combination is actually wild.
Jesus.
Well, okay.
Okay, then.
I like it.
Oh, that's a...
That's a solid digger right there.
Ha!
That...
Why is that so good?
Dude, that's my digger.
Okay, I have some insane stuff already, actually.
This is wild.
All right, I'm gonna...
I'm actually gonna get this.
I'm gonna try it.
Let's see how often this actually happens.
Wait, crit is five times the damage, no?
Oh, it's not looking good.
This seems like it.
Forty-five.
This does not look very good.
This kind of sucks.
Not gonna lie.
Yikes.
And we're gonna have a black hole, of course.
Maybe put it on...
this one, just because...
No, okay, we can't.
All right.
Long-distance cast...
Do we want a long-distance cast something?
Cast zero?
Oh, it's shuffle, of course.
Never mind.
Fucking shuffle.
All right.
What else do I buy?
What's that one?
Delayed.
And remind me exactly what this does.
A static, magical phenomenon that casts three extra spells after a short while.
But it's only the spells that come after?
Right.
Oh, but I need three spells here, I guess.
Okay.
I wonder when that is good.
When would that be good?
Maybe actually with this.
No, hold on.
Disc projectile.
Maybe I want this one as well.
Because this actually...
Wait a minute.
Oh, that costs 30 mana, that's right.
Wait, why does the digging bolt cost zero mana?
What the fuck?
This thing is nuts!
All right.
Well, we're moving on.
And because we can't really...
Oh, can we?
No.
I'm gonna say we cannot kill Stuart.
I am leaving.
We're playing this safe.
No bullshit.
Oh my god, the digging is real already!
Oh, dude.
I feel like I've gotten way better at just making digging stuff.
And this wand I have here is...
Okay, okay, I crit quite a lot actually, it seems.
Maybe the crit doesn't work on the statue or whatever.
Oh, look, I crit again.
Not bad.
Not bad, I say.
And that's right, I said it.
Uh-oh.
What's happening here?
Oh, you're down there.
Okay, huh.
Actually,
go up again.
Also, I keep wanting to change to my second wand so I can teleport, but be careful because that's a black hole.
So you know what?
I'm gonna put it on four just to be safe here.
I will accidentally teleport somewhere and fuck it up for sure.
Or try to teleport somewhere.
Why am I getting in here?
Right, money.
What's up fools?
Oh yeah, and the lava burns, the enemy's perfect.
Beautiful.
Like a symphony.
Symphony of death.
The digging!
The crit is real too.
67 damage on a crit from a freaking spark bolt.
Look at all this gold I'm accruing.
Is that the right word?
Accruing?
I have accrued wealth.
I think so.
Accrue.
Amassed.
I have amassed a bunch of money.
Go this way.
Dap that.
Here we go.
This way.
Oh my god.
I'm like a worm!
It feels so good!
Oh yeah!
It's not even super fast either.
Like this can definitely dig even faster later on.
Oh, that's a lot of lava.
Dude, can you believe that I fucking turned lava into...
What was it, pea soup?
That is the best thing ever!
Holy crap, man.
Oh, hold on, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
200% pheromone for me, baby!
I'll take it.
Go fuck yourself now.
Oh, I don't like the acid though.
All right, it's gonna evaporate.
Just wait, just wait.
Don't break the potion.
Oh wait, is the acid gonna break the potion?
Oh no.
Don't do it, acid!
Don't do it!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Yoink!
That's for future Trevor.
Trevor's college fund has been secured.
Come on.
Oh, that's tough rock.
We're not gonna get through that.
I don't like that at all.
Keep going.
Wow, that was lucky.
Whoa, 162 crit?
Wait, is that because...
Wait, how did that crit 162?
I don't understand.
This one times five.
Fifteen.
What's that times five?
That's not, that's no way.
Or maybe together.
Hmm, 16 times five?
That's not enough either.
How did that crit for so much?
There's something I'm not getting.
Yeah.
Oh my god.
Know what I love about the spark bolt?
It has almost no drop off.
It's so precise.
It's super delicious.
Like whoever put the lamp right above the coal is a goddamn idiot.
Whoa.
Oh, that up gold.
Wait.
Oh, I understand.
You see, I have like the berserkium visual effect on me all the time.
I think it's because of that critical hit plus.
I just kept thinking, wait, did I just pick up some circum somehow?
Oh, so much lava.
Rocks.
I'll take it.
Can't get enough of that.
And who knows?
Maybe I'll get lucky with unlimited spells.
One of my favorite perks.
Hey, I said explode.
What?
All right, fine.
Be that way.
What's up, guys?
What do we got?
I mean, the one is not terrible.
0.27.
Lots of slots.
Low spread.
Decent capacity.
Not bad.
It's pretty much a better version of this.
I will replace...
No.
Yes.
Hold on.
That's a tough one.
Fuck this.
Chances of finding unlimited spells.
Pretty low anyway.
And I can always come back for this if I absolutely find that, right?
I know there's some one somewhere.
So if I really want to and I find unlimited, I could always come back and I will spend some time and I'll find it.
I'm making lots of justifications for my actions here.
Yo.
Nah.
I once had great love for the glowing lands, but that has subsided quite a bit since.
It's just not what it used to be, you know?
It doesn't hit the same way.
It used to hit the sweet spot just right.
Nowadays, it comes in at an awkward angle and it's just not quite the same.
I want to dig.
Nah, I don't want to dig.
What's this here?
What?
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
The air feels extremely humid.
All right.
Oh, that's steam.
Nice.
I thought it was a freezing vapor.
There's a wand down there.
Oh, there's oil.
We got to wait for that.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Dude, we got to get high.
Wait, my spells are slowing down over there.
Oh, is that because of the humus?
Humidity?
I think it is.
That's the humidity right there.
That's what that does.
Always casts, makes a particular separate into a bundle of five explosive bolts as soon as it moves.
Oh,
but their spells is also slow.
Concentrated mana.
Oh, well, you know what?
Maybe I'll take that.
Thank you.
You may ask yourself, why am I going in here?
And the question, the answer to that is...
because I'm not afraid.
I have a decent wand and I do good damage.
Asshole.
Oh, we're going to get high.
I think we're going to get high, guys.
Don't you hit me with that, whatever that is.
What is this music?
I haven't heard this music before.
All right, let's, let's eat.
Is that enough?
Oh, I'm puking now.
More.
Oh, that's enough.
Worm blood.
Oh, interesting.
Oh, but wait, that's bad.
Then I can never use worm blood, I guess.
Oh, shit.
Kivaskivi.
Yo, look at all these flasks.
What's going on there?
Oh, hello.
Oh, wait.
Oh, it's going to destroy the flask.
I'm an idiot.
Come here.
Yes, come here.
There we go.
Now die.
All right, I'm going to go around.
Blow up.
Good.
There's a wand up there too.
Hold on, hold on.
That's pretty dope.
Is that not pretty dope?
Oh, that's a long recharge.
Wait, it shoots eight spells?
That's the ultimate shotgun.
Holy crap.
That's fun.
Let's try it.
And that's just a potion.
What?
What does that even mean?
Uh, let's drink all this.
Get rid of that.
Wait, what?
Mimikion potion?
The fuck is that?
I can't pick it up.
Huh?
Wait, it's an enemy.
Look, it's affected by something.
Uh-oh.
What the hell?
Hold on a second.
What's happening here?
I'm going to try and kill it.
Huh?
I have never seen that.
Interesting.
Pretty cool.
I like it.
Concentrate a mana, levitation.
I think I'll take that.
That's also an enemy.
Fucking hell.
Now we have a vine.
Wait, what?
Uh-oh.
Hide!
Hold on.
I'm going to shotgun him.
That's not the shotgun.
Ah, la-la-la-la-la-la-la.
What the fuck is happening?
Oh, wait, the acid is through.
That's perfect.
I need to get in here.
Can I get in?
I can.
Oh, that's shitty.
Never mind.
Another chest.
Sweet.
Dude, there's a lot of potions in the fungal caverns.
There we go.
Hold on, let me get, let this guy get close, and then we shotgun him to death.
That's how we do it.
Beautiful stuff.
And the reason that works, guys, is because he has a shield on, and the shotgun shoots a million shells at the same time.
In Vesipulium now.
Oh my god, all the potions.
I guess I'll take some levitation while we're doing this, anyway.
Boink.
Flamoxio, too.
Oh, I can't get in there.
Yes, I can!
What am I talking about?
I have black holes!
Oh, but hold on.
There's flasks, too.
Let's be careful.
That's empty.
Boing.
Oh, the air is humid.
That's fine, actually.
That actually works out in my favor, I think.
Lava potion.
Okay.
Summon egg.
How's the wand?
Wand is, like, weird.
I don't think I like any of this.
That much.
Yeah.
So, there's also this circle on this one, similar to the rock.
Golden circle.
What could that mean?
Maybe, like...
I don't know.
Like, a round object that follows an arch when you...
Whoa!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Those guys are scary.
Can I even kill him?
Oh, not these fucking thingies.
They're so awkward, moving slowly.
Why am I so...
Oh, I ate way too much.
Somehow.
That's not good.
Lava potion.
Oh, shit, I'm on fire.
Oh, shit, he's...
Oh, man.
This guy doesn't fuck around.
Can I get in here?
I can.
Maybe I just ignore him.
Fuck you, man.
Fuck yeah, extra health for me.
So far, it's been totally worth it coming in here.
But I gotta get high again.
Oof.
Wait, can I even...
Oh, it makes me more full when I eat it.
Okay, we can't get high yet.
Shit.
I don't want to be this slow, man, we gotta wait.
Hey, look at this!
Very nice.
Let's get rid of that one.
Wrap that.
And we have a wand here, too.
Not feeling it.
Man, is there a way to get rid of this satiation quicker?
Gosh, this guy again.
Oh, man, these guys are super difficult.
Maybe I just leave.
Yeah, you know what, 65 HP, we've done enough in here.
We've done enough.
And, oh, hold on.
There's a wand up there, too.
A slimy egg.
What are we working with?
Oh, it's the same one I checked before.
Oh, look at this!
Another pro...
Oh my goodness.
Oh, it makes me full!
Wait, what?
Choking and bloated.
Okay, you know what?
Don't...
No more.
No more eating.
I lost some health there, too.
Okay, so overeating is bad.
It's really bad.
What does that mean?
Choking?
Clumsy movement.
Any more food or drinking will hurt you.
Ooh!
Okay.
We're not getting high.
I can tell you that much.
We're done getting high.
That's news to me, all that.
Maybe I do understand that perk now.
Okay, so I think it's actually just time to leave.
This is it, guys.
We're leaving.
We've done enough here.
We have 2,000 monies and shit.
This is actually great.
We're doing really well.
All right, let's find a way down.
And here we are.
I have a nose for these things.
Okay.
Damn, I'm full.
I'm in a food coma.
Nice!
Add mana?
What's this one?
Bloodlust.
Oh, is that the one that...
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Ooh.
Ooh, that's a bit scary.
Because I have a memory of something terrible.
Gold is for...
What?
Oh, I see, I see, I see.
Okay, yeah.
No, no, I don't want that.
Homonculus.
Boming sh...
No.
Ah, that's not bad.
Actually not bad.
I'm greedy.
Hey, speak enough.
No.
No, I hated that one.
I hated that one, nevermind.
Spell supply faster?
Uhhh...
I feel like I'm going into the rabbit hole with spending all my money right now.
Hold on.
Let's just get the essentials over here first.
Before we do anything drastic.
That one.
Pretty much essential.
What's that?
Bible thrower.
This one.
And...
Maybe that one.
And maybe...
Only maybe saw blade.
I'm gonna reroll one more time.
Come on now.
Boomerang?
No.
Oh, these...
These suck.
Okay, I guess I'm coming back later.
I don't want any of them.
That's unfortunate.
But we got ad mana, and that's big.
That's actually really big.
So, check this out.
Maybe we can do something crazy here.
This shoots eight spells per cast, right?
So does that actually mean that...
Wait,
does it actually mean that?
Oh, okay, hold on.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
Maybe like that.
Weird.
Very slow, too.
Oh, this one adds castile.
Oh, but the recharge time is already super high.
But...
No.
Eh?
That one actually...
Let me think.
0.18.
0.17.
Yo, this one is actually good.
Kind of nuts.
But it's shuffle.
But that...
Does that mean...
Wait.
Is that always applying still, though?
So if I shoot...
If this gets shot, it shoots this one and that.
But then if it shoots this...
Nothing happens.
Yeah, sometimes I see this shot in front of me here.
Is that better?
Let me see.
This one is more consistent, but it's slower.
But I think this one is actually about the same.
Consistency-wise.
Like that...
That's better.
That's straight up better.
Even though it's shuffle.
That's wild.
Or...
Hold on.
Throw an ad mana in there.
No, that's way too unpredictable.
Maybe we do something like that up here.
Oh, but hold on.
The recharge is shit on this.
That's a conundrum.
That's annoying.
But I mean, I guess I made an okay want here.
Like this actually works pretty well.
Energy orb.
This costs 30 mana?
This one adds 30 mana.
So can we do something fun there?
Also, just throw this in there.
No, this costs too much mana.
Let's say we do...
That.
Oh, but this is still too slow though.
How fast does this shoot?
It's not bad.
I mean, we don't need this, I guess.
We have this.
Yeah, fuck that.
Feels kind of weird not using the ad mana.
Right?
But I guess that's how it is.
I guess I could use the bloodlust and just not...
I could have a bloodlust wand.
And just be careful with it.
Right?
That is a thing I could do.
Like a spark bolt on that.
A simple one.
A simple spark bolt, maybe.
That's not too dangerous.
I could throw it down here.
I mean, it's a bit scary, isn't it?
But look at that.
Look at that damage, dude.
It's very tempting.
Kind of slow though.
Wait a second.
I hate shovel wands.
I can't wait to find a decent non-shuffle wand right now.
That's actually the only thing limiting me.
And we throw this one in there as well.
What if we don't have it?
Oh, we don't need it, okay.
But this one.
With mana.
Not that good.
Okay, I guess this is what we're doing then.
Yeah.
Maybe we can have some fun with a long distance cast on one of these.
Maybe some long distance.
Just something long distance.
Just to kill something, you know.
And then have something like that.
And maybe energy orb.
Like that does a decent amount of damage.
So does this.
Shoot through walls a bit.
Always fun.
And then...
But I would like to cast more, because if it's a one-shot deal anyway, do as much damage as I can.
Oh wait, this only affects that one though.
Or does it?
Yeah, it does.
That's the...
Yeah, we need a triple spell something like that for that to work.
Yikes.
Okay.
I think I'll put this on one of the wands.
Put it on this one.
And now I'm going.
I gotta come back here.
Do we have the capability to kill Stuart?
I'm gonna say no.
We don't.
Oh yeah.
Levitation.
Oh, I'm doing solid damage here.
This is some good shit.
But it's scary.
Because it hurts me too.
I mean, I just gotta find enough HP, then I'm good, right?
Hey, problem solved.
Easy money.
And the digging is still good.
Ooh, what's going on?
What is going on there?
Is that you?
I think it was.
How do I get to you?
Slowly.
Yeah, I do solid damage.
That's really nice.
Oh, but I'm very imprecise.
Why is that?
Oh, this adds a bit of spread as well.
And this one has inherent spread.
So that's like 12 degrees of spread.
Right there.
So long distance, not the greatest.
Just kind of ironic, because it's a spark bolt.
But it's good enough.
Wait, what are you shooting?
Ooh, okay.
What's this?
Eh?
Die, please.
Good.
Oh, ouch.
Got a rat bite.
Hopefully no plague is in me now.
All right, we're here.
Oh, wait.
We could actually do something here.
We could get some HP.
Shit, I forgot about the black hole.
Fuck!
I completely forgot about that.
Dammit.
But I was going to go up, and next to the racetrack, I was going to get the HP there.
Yeah.
I'll take it.
Very... not precise at long range.
Look at all these fools.
Fuck!
Getting hits on me here.
That's not good.
Wait, I've seen this exact thing before.
Remember, I teleported in, teleported in, teleported out, teleported out.
Kind of funny seeing these similar level elements in different combinations.
It's actually going pretty well.
We even have pheromone ready, and more pheromone.
Nah, I'll leave it.
Wait,
did he die from the collapse?
No fucking way.
That's awesome.
Him and all his friends.
Whoa, oh, I'm stunned.
Hide in the water.
89 HP.
It's not great.
What do we got here?
Ooh, interesting.
I don't think so.
Nope.
Not today.
Drain it.
All right, we're reaching the point where it's time to go home, I think.
Yeah, we keep taking damage here.
This is bad.
That's another sniper.
Gonna burn alive.
Whoa!
Okay, yeah, we're leaving.
One more hit and I'm down.
Take it easy, take it easy.
Shit, shit.
That's unreal.
That's...
Oh, the portal was right there as well.
Oh, that's unreal.
Oh, fuck.
Oh no, it was such a good run as well, man.
Ah, damn it.
I gotta quit here anyway, guys.
It's been a long stream.
I gotta get up early tomorrow and write code.
Damn it, I wanted to fill out more of the map today as well.
There's so many things I wanna do.
This game is brutal, dude.
Absolutely brutal.
I may just jump right out, guys.
I gotta get some food.
Oh, shit, the store closed.
Actually, that's okay.
I have some food left.
Oliver, you need to use restart with mods instead of save and quit to quickly restart.
Oh, okay.
Right.
Okay, I'm gonna do that.
But one of these times when I went out, I also deleted or not deleted, I copied my save folder just to be safe.
So I think it's good that I went out and then went straight in after without doing the immediate restart.
Right?
Maybe you don't wanna copy the things while the game is running.
Yeah, all right, guys.
Thank you so much for watching.
This was actually a blast today.
I really had fun.
Hopefully next time we can...
We discovered a bunch of stuff as well.
Next time is the time where we get a sick run going.
I believe it.
I'm gonna put a raid on, of course.
I got a raid annoyed streamer.
That's always fun.
How about...
Finally back to the basics.
No purgatory.
I don't know what that means.
But let's go.
Let's freaking go, guys.
I'll see you guys around.
Thanks for watching.
Have a great night.
Bye-bye.